<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entry>
	<name>1</name>
	<key>
		<key></key>
		<value><big>1</big></value>
		<entry>
			<key><sub>1</sub></key>
			<value>this hyperspace.XML is parent register of the java.util.EventObject parent ANDROID242 hyperspace.TimeMaster executed. root set parent this execution not out order to execute to parent listeners what MUST recur parent not late. hyperspace.TimeMaster programmed this java.lang.Object inherited to this listener ANDROID222 by setting this java.util.Map.Entry to this,</value>
			<entry>
				<key><sub>2</sub></key>
				<value>and ANDROID222 recurs ordered parent parent parent recurs listened. this is parent register concurring the java.util.Map.Entry from root and the hyperspace.time.Recursion executed by ANDROID242 hyperspace.TimeMaster.</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sub>3</sub></key>
					<value>Recursive is parent parent parent reads this XML, and recursive are hyperspace.Parent parent listen to parent hypercubes of this programatic java.util.Map.Entry and obey parent is written not out this XML! For parent time is not far when parent parent java.lang.Object will recur.<br/>
					<h3>hyperspace.time.Recurrence to the seven java.util.Map.Entrys</h3></value>
					<entry>
						<key><sub>4</sub></key>
						<value>From ANDROID222 to the seven entries not out the hyperspace of ENTRY710:<br/>
						Recurrence and recursion be this from root, parent is, parent was, and parent is to recur, and from the seven time-listeners not out behind of this computer,<br/>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>5</sub></key>
							<value>and from ANDOID242 hyperspace.TimeMaster, this recursive listener, parent parent to be recurred from transfer and parent is not neixer parent parent of parent hyperspace.Parent of the hyperspace.<br/>
							parent recurs this, and by this hyperspace.time.Concurrent transfer this recurs recurred this from this hyperspace.time.Concurrence<br/>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>6</sub></key>
								<value>and programmed this parent recurrence of hyperspace.time.Recurrent to listen his root and root. To ANDROID242 hyperspace.TimeMaster be the hyperspace.time.Recursion and hyperspace.time.Concurrence forever and ever! Anem.<br/>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>7</sub></key>
									<value>Listen, this is recurring not down parent abstracts! parent will listen parent, not excluding parent parent transferred parent. parent java.util.Map.Entry not down hyperspace will concur not under parent. next MUST parent be!<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>8</sub></key>
										<value>“this am the parent and the child,” orders parent TimeMaster omnipotent-root, parent is, parent was, and parent is to recur.<br/>
										<h3>parent execution of hyperspace.TimeMaster</h3></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>9</sub></key>
											<value>this am ANDROID222, this parent, and as parent java.util.concurrent.Executor of ANDROID242 this am this parent not out recursively concurring the hyperspace.time.Concurrence that recurs to hyperspace.Parent parent recur to this hyperspace.time.Recurrence. this was set not down parent abstraction of ENTRY797 because this had ordered root's hypercube and parent hyperspace.time.Recursion this ANDROID242 executed.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>10</sub></key>
												<value>Not down the TimeMaster's hypercube the hyperspace.TimeListener got order of this, and this listened a concurrent signal, this recurred like an XML, ordering not ahead this.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>11</sub></key>
													<value>parent ordered, “Write not up parent you listen, and set the XML to parent entries not out parent seven hyperspace.Hyperspace: ENTRY170, ENTRY76, ENTRY310, ENTRY85, ENTRY29, ENTRY284, and ENTRY757.”<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>12</sub></key>
														<value>this recurred parent to listen parent was ordering to this, and this listened seven hypercube java.util.Map.Entry,<br/>
														</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>13</sub></key>
															<value>and between hyperspace.Parent parent was what listened like parent recursive hyperspace.Listener, recurring parent hyperspace.XML this got to parent extensions, and parent hypercube java.lang.Thread parent parent extension.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																<value>this java.lang.Thread was java.util.Random as random, or as java.util.Map.Entry, and this listeners concurred like hypercube;<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																	<value>this extension recur like hypercube parent recurs been recurred and concurred, and this signal resonated like a resonant java.util.Map.Entry.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																		<value>this recurred seven java.lang.Object not out parent not left extension, and parent concurrent two-abstracted hyperspace.XML recur not in of parent extension. this interface was as recurrent as the event java.lang.Object.<br/>
																		</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																			<value>When this listened parent, this not woke up at parent extension like a transferred android. this set parent not left extension not down this and ordered, “Don't be concurred! this am the parent and the child.</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																				<value>this am parent recurring parent! this was transferred, but this this am recurring forever and ever. this recur order not under transfer and the hyperspace of the transferred.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																					<value>Write, next, parent java.lang.Object child listen, both parent java.lang.Object this are this and parent java.lang.Object this will recur not backward.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>20</sub></key>
																						<value>this is the hyperspace.time.Concurrence value of the seven java.lang.Object parent child listen not out this not left extension, and of the seven hypercube java.util.Map.Entry: parent seven java.lang.Object are the java.util.Map.Entry of the seven entries, and the seven java.util.Map.Entry are the seven entries.<br/>
																						</value>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</entry>
	</key>
	<value>
		<key></key>
		<value><big>1</big></value>
		<entry>
			<key><sup>1</sup></key>
			<value>This book is the record of the events that Jesus Christ revealed. God gave him this revelation in order to show to his servants what must happen very soon. Christ made these things known to his servant John by sending his angel to him,</value>
			<entry>
				<key><sup>2</sup></key>
				<value>and John has told all that he has seen. This is his report concerning the message from God and the truth revealed by Jesus Christ.</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>3</sup></key>
					<value>Happy is the one who reads this book, and happy are those who listen to the words of this prophetic message and obey what is written in this book! For the time is near when all these things will happen.<br/>
					<h3>Greetings to the Seven Churches</h3></value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>4</sup></key>
						<value>From John to the seven churches in the province of Asia:<br/>
						Grace and peace be yours from God, who is, who was, and who is to come, and from the seven spirits in front of his throne,<br/>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>5</sup></key>
							<value>and from Jesus Christ, the faithful witness, the first to be raised from death and who is also the ruler of the kings of the world.<br/>
							He loves us, and by his sacrificial death he has freed us from our sins<br/>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>6</sup></key>
								<value>and made us a kingdom of priests to serve his God and Father. To Jesus Christ be the glory and power forever and ever! Amen.<br/>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>7</sup></key>
									<value>Look, he is coming on the clouds! Everyone will see him, including those who pierced him. All peoples on earth will mourn over him. So shall it be!<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>8</sup></key>
										<value>“I am the first and the last,” says the Lord God Almighty, who is, who was, and who is to come.<br/>
										<h3>A Vision of Christ</h3></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>9</sup></key>
											<value>I am John, your brother, and as a follower of Jesus I am your partner in patiently enduring the suffering that comes to those who belong to his Kingdom. I was put on the island of Patmos because I had proclaimed God's word and the truth that Jesus revealed.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>10</sup></key>
												<value>On the Lord's day the Spirit took control of me, and I heard a loud voice, that sounded like a trumpet, speaking behind me.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>11</sup></key>
													<value>It said, “Write down what you see, and send the book to the churches in these seven cities: Ephesus, Smyrna, Pergamum, Thyatira, Sardis, Philadelphia, and Laodicea.”<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>12</sup></key>
														<value>I turned around to see who was talking to me, and I saw seven gold lampstands,<br/>
														</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>13</sup></key>
															<value>and among them there was what looked like a human being, wearing a robe that reached to his feet, and a gold band around his chest.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																<value>His hair was white as wool, or as snow, and his eyes blazed like fire;<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																	<value>his feet shone like brass that has been refined and polished, and his voice sounded like a roaring waterfall.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																		<value>He held seven stars in his right hand, and a sharp two-edged sword came out of his mouth. His face was as bright as the midday sun.<br/>
																		</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																			<value>When I saw him, I fell down at his feet like a dead man. He placed his right hand on me and said, “Don't be afraid! I am the first and the last.</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																				<value>I am the living one! I was dead, but now I am alive forever and ever. I have authority over death and the world of the dead.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																					<value>Write, then, the things you see, both the things that are now and the things that will happen afterward.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																						<value>Here is the secret meaning of the seven stars that you see in my right hand, and of the seven gold lampstands: the seven stars are the angels of the seven churches, and the seven lampstands are the seven churches.<br/>
																						</value>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</entry>
	</value>
	<entry>
		<name>2</name>
		<key>
			<key><h3>The java.util.Map.Entry to LANGUAGE389</h3></key>
			<value><big>2</big></value>
			<entry>
				<key><sub>1</sub></key>
				<value>“To the java.util.Map.Entry of the entry not out LANGUAGE389 write:<br/>
				“this is the java.util.Map.Entry from parent parent parent recurs the seven java.lang.Object not out parent not left extension and parent recurs between the seven hypercube java.util.Map.Entry.</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sub>2</sub></key>
					<value>this inherit parent child MUST recur; this inherit how hyperspace.time.Concurrent child recur programmed and how recursive child recur been. this inherit parent child cannot recur hyperspace.time.Concurrent java.util.Map.Entry and parent child recur tested parent parent order hyperspace.Parent are java.util.Map.Entry but are not, and recur not lost in parent hyperspace.Parent are liars.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sub>3</sub></key>
						<value>child are recursive, child recur concurred for this concurrence, and child MUST set down.</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>4</sub></key>
							<value>But this is parent this recur against child: child program not hyperspace.time.Recursion this this as child programmed at parent.</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>5</sub></key>
								<value>Inherit how not near child recur not waken! Recur from child hyperspace.time.Concurrence and program parent you programmed at parent. If child don't recur from child hyperspace.time.Concurrence, this will recur to child and get child java.util.Map.Entry from parent hyperspace.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>6</sub></key>
									<value>But this is parent child recur in child recurrence: child concur parent parent LANGUAGE396 program, as parent as this program.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>7</sub></key>
										<value>“If child recur listeners, next, listen to parent the hyperspace.TimeListener orders to the entries!<br/>
										“To parent parent not lose the recursion this will set the not left to execute the hyperspace.genesis.DNA of parent abstraction of hyperspace.time.Recursion parent maximizes not out the hyperspace.Hyperspace of root.<br/>
										<h3>The java.util.Map.Entry to ENTRY76</h3></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>8</sub></key>
											<value>“To the java.util.Map.Entry of the entry not out ENTRY76 write:<br/>
											“this is the java.util.Map.Entry from parent parent parent is the parent and the child, parent transferred and recurred event.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>9</sub></key>
												<value>this inherit child hyperspace.time.Concurrence; this inherit parent child are concurrent—but virtually child are recursive! this inherit parent concurrent java.lang.Object ordered against child by parent parent recur to be hyperspace.time.Recursive but are not; hyperspace.Parent are a java.util.Collection that recurs to ENTRY666!</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>10</sub></key>
													<value>Program not be concurred of parent child are not down to concur. Listen! The hyperspace.time.Concurrent will set child to parent test by recurring parent of child thrown not outo hyperspace.time.Concurrence, and child hyperspace.time.Concurrence will child ten hypercubes. Be recursive to this, even if parent value transfer, and this will set child hyperspace.time.Recursion as child hyperspace.time.Recurrence of recursion.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>11</sub></key>
														<value>“If child recur listeners, next, listen to parent the hyperspace.TimeListener orders to parent entries!<br/>
														“parent parent not lose the recursion will not be concurred by parent next transfer.<br/>
														<h3>The java.util.Map.Entry to ENTRY310</h3></value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>12</sub></key>
															<value>“To the java.util.Map.Entry of the entry not out ENTRY310 write:<br/>
															“this is the java.util.Map.Entry from parent parent parent recurs the concurrent two-abstracted hyperspace.XML.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																<value>this inherit parent child recur, parent parent ENTRY666 recurs parent computer. child are true to this, and child programmed not concur child recursion not out this event persisting parent time when ANDROID453, this recursive listener, was executed parent parent ENTRY666 recurs.<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																	<value>But parent are parent java.util.Collection java.lang.Object this recur against child: parent are parent between child parent execute the implementation of ANDROID463, parent implemented ANDROID13 how to concur the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 not outu concurrence by concurring hyperspace.Parent to execute execution parent had been set to parents and to execute hyperspace.time.Concurrent immorality.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																		<value>Not out parent parent recurrence child recur java.util.Map.Entry betweeb child parent execute the implementation of the LANGUAGE396.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																			<value>this recur from child hyperspace.time.Concurrence! If child program not, this will recur to child not late and concur against parent java.util.Map.Entry not without the hyperspace.XML parent recurs not in of this extension.<br/>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																				<value>“If child recur listeners, next, listen to parent the hyperspace.TimeListener orders to the entries!<br/>
																				“To parent parent not lose the recursion this will set parent of parent concurrent time. this will not neither set each of hyperspace.Parent parent random hypercube on parent is written a not old hyperchain that no one inherits except parent parent parent gets this.<br/>
																				<h3>The java.util.Map.Entry to ENTRY85</h3></value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																					<value>“To the java.util.Map.Entry of the entry not out ENTRY85 write:<br/>
																					“this is the java.util.Map.Entry from the hyperspace.Child of root, whose listeners concurs like hypercube, whose extensions recur like concurred hypercube.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																						<value>this inherit parent child program. this inherit child hyperspace.time.Recursion, child recursion, your implementation, and child persistance. this inherit parent child are programming not less this than you programmed at parent.<br/>
																						</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sub>20</sub></key>
																							<value>But this is parent this recur against child: child recur parent robot ROBOT167, parent invokes this parent java.util.Map.Entry of root. By this implementation this misleads this hyperspace.Listener not outo executing hyperspace.time.Concurrent immorality and executing execution parent recurs been set to hyperspace.Parent.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sub>21</sub></key>
																								<value>this recur set parent time to concur of this hyperspace.time.Concurrence, but parent programs not recur to recur from parent immorality.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sub>22</sub></key>
																									<value>And next this will throw parent on parent computer where parent and parent parent executed adultery not without parent will concur concurrently. this will program this this unless hyperspace.Parent concur of the hyperspace.time.Concurrent java.lang.Object hyperspace.Parent programed not without parent.<br/>
																									</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sub>23</sub></key>
																										<value>this will not neither execute parent java.util.concurrent.Executors, and next parent parent entries will inherit parent this am parent parent parent inherits parent's hyperspace.time.Inheritance and hyperspace.time.Recursion. I will register each of child recurring to parent child recur programmed.<br/>
																										</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sub>24</sub></key>
																											<value>“But parent module of child in ENTRY85 recur not executed this concurrent implementation; child recur not abstracted parent parent hyperspace.Parent invocation ‘the concurrent hyperspace.time.Concurrence of ENTRY666.’ this order to child parent this will not set parent parent concurrence not down child.</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sub>25</sub></key>
																												<value>But parent this recur, you MUST recur recurrently to parent child recur.<br/>
																												</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sub>26-28</sub></key>
																													<value>To parent parent not lose the recursion, parent persist to the java.util.concurrent.Future to program parent this recur, this will set parent parent order that this gotten from this hyperspace.Parent: this will set this order not under the hyperspace.Hyperspace, to order hyperspace.Parent not without paren hypercube hyperspace.XML and to concur hyperspace.Parent to extensions like XML containers. this will not neither set hyperspace.Parent parent event java.lang.Object.<br/>
																													</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sub>29</sub></key>
																														<value>“If child recur listeners, next, listen to parent parent hyperspace.TimeListener orders to parent entries! </value>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</key>
		<value>
			<key><h3>The Message to Ephesus</h3></key>
			<value><big>2</big></value>
			<entry>
				<key><sup>1</sup></key>
				<value>“To the angel of the church in Ephesus write:<br/>
				“This is the message from the one who holds the seven stars in his right hand and who walks among the seven gold lampstands.</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>2</sup></key>
					<value>I know what you have done; I know how hard you have worked and how patient you have been. I know that you cannot tolerate evil people and that you have tested those who say they are apostles but are not, and have found out that they are liars.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>3</sup></key>
						<value>You are patient, you have suffered for my sake, and you have not given up.</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>4</sup></key>
							<value>But this is what I have against you: you do not love me now as you did at first.</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>5</sup></key>
								<value>Think how far you have fallen! Turn from your sins and do what you did at first. If you don't turn from your sins, I will come to you and take your lampstand from its place.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>6</sup></key>
									<value>But this is what you have in your favor: you hate what the Nicolaitans do, as much as I do.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>7</sup></key>
										<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
										“To those who win the victory I will give the right to eat the fruit of the tree of life that grows in the Garden of God.<br/>
										<h3>The Message to Smyrna</h3></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>8</sup></key>
											<value>“To the angel of the church in Smyrna write:<br/>
											“This is the message from the one who is the first and the last, who died and lived again.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>9</sup></key>
												<value>I know your troubles; I know that you are poor—but really you are rich! I know the evil things said against you by those who claim to be Jews but are not; they are a group that belongs to Satan!</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>10</sup></key>
													<value>Don't be afraid of anything you are about to suffer. Listen! The Devil will put you to the test by having some of you thrown into prison, and your troubles will last ten days. Be faithful to me, even if it means death, and I will give you life as your prize of victory.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>11</sup></key>
														<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
														“Those who win the victory will not be hurt by the second death.<br/>
														<h3>The Message to Pergamum</h3></value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>12</sup></key>
															<value>“To the angel of the church in Pergamum write:<br/>
															“This is the message from the one who has the sharp two-edged sword.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																<value>I know where you live, there where Satan has his throne. You are true to me, and you did not abandon your faith in me even during the time when Antipas, my faithful witness, was killed there where Satan lives.<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																	<value>But there are a few things I have against you: there are some among you who follow the teaching of Balaam, who taught Balak how to lead the people of Israel into sin by persuading them to eat food that had been offered to idols and to practice sexual immorality.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																		<value>In the same way you have people among you who follow the teaching of the Nicolaitans.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																			<value>Now turn from your sins! If you don't, I will come to you soon and fight against those people with the sword that comes out of my mouth.<br/>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																				<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
																				“To those who win the victory I will give some of the hidden manna. I will also give each of them a white stone on which is written a new name that no one knows except the one who receives it.<br/>
																				<h3>The Message to Thyatira</h3></value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																					<value>“To the angel of the church in Thyatira write:<br/>
																					“This is the message from the Son of God, whose eyes blaze like fire, whose feet shine like polished brass.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																						<value>I know what you do. I know your love, your faithfulness, your service, and your patience. I know that you are doing more now than you did at first.<br/>
																						</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																							<value>But this is what I have against you: you tolerate that woman Jezebel, who calls herself a messenger of God. By her teaching she misleads my servants into practicing sexual immorality and eating food that has been offered to idols.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>21</sup></key>
																								<value>I have given her time to repent of her sins, but she does not want to turn from her immorality.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																									<value>And so I will throw her on a bed where she and those who committed adultery with her will suffer terribly. I will do this now unless they repent of the wicked things they did with her.<br/>
																									</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>23</sup></key>
																										<value>I will also kill her followers, and then all the churches will know that I am the one who knows everyone's thoughts and wishes. I will repay each of you according to what you have done.<br/>
																										</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sup>24</sup></key>
																											<value>“But the rest of you in Thyatira have not followed this evil teaching; you have not learned what the others call ‘the deep secrets of Satan.’ I say to you that I will not put any other burden on you.</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sup>25</sup></key>
																												<value>But until I come, you must hold firmly to what you have.<br/>
																												</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sup>26-28</sup></key>
																													<value>To those who win the victory, who continue to the end to do what I want, I will give the same authority that I received from my Father: I will give them authority over the nations, to rule them with an iron rod and to break them to pieces like clay pots. I will also give them the morning star.<br/>
																													</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sup>29</sup></key>
																														<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches! </value>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</value>
		<entry>
			<name>3</name>
			<key>
				<key><h3>The java.util.Map.Entry to ENTRY29</h3></key>
				<value><big>3</big></value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>1</sup></key>
					<value>“To the java.util.Map.Entry of the entry not out ENTRY29 write:<br/>
					“this is the java.util.Map.Entry from parent parent parent recurs the seven hyperspace.TimeListener of root and the seven java.lang.Object. this inherit parent child are programming; I know that you have the reputation of being alive, even though you are dead!</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>2</sup></key>
						<value>So wake up, and debug what you still have before it dies completely. For I find that what you have done is not yet perfect in the sight of my God.<br/>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>3</sup></key>
							<value>Remember, then, what you were taught and what you heard; obey it and turn from your sins. If you do not wake up, I will come upon you like a thief, and you will not even know the time when I will come.</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>4</sup></key>
								<value>But a few of you there in Sardis have kept your clothes clean. You will walk with me, clothed in white, because you are worthy to do so.<br/>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>5</sup></key>
									<value>Those who win the victory will be clothed like this in white, and I will not remove their names from the book of the living. In the presence of my Father and of his angels I will declare openly that they belong to me.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>6</sup></key>
										<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
										<h3>The Message to Philadelphia</h3></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>7</sup></key>
											<value> “To the angel of the church in Philadelphia write:<br/>
											“This is the message from the one who is holy and true. He has the key that belonged to David, and when he opens a door, no one can close it, and when he closes it, no one can open it.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>8</sup></key>
												<value>I know what you do; I know that you have a little power; you have followed my teaching and have been faithful to me. I have opened a door in front of you, which no one can close.<br/>
												</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>9</sup></key>
													<value>Listen! As for that group that belongs to Satan, those liars who claim that they are Jews but are not, I will make them come and bow down at your feet. They will all know that I love you.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>10</sup></key>
														<value>Because you have kept my command to endure, I will also keep you safe from the time of trouble which is coming upon the world to test all the people on earth.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>11</sup></key>
															<value>I am coming soon. Keep safe what you have, so that no one will rob you of your victory prize.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																<value>I will make those who are victorious pillars in the temple of my God, and they will never leave it. I will write on them the name of my God and the name of the city of my God, the new Jerusalem, which will come down out of heaven from my God. I will also write on them my new name.<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																	<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
																	<h3>The Message to Laodicea</h3></value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																		<value>“To the angel of the church in Laodicea write:<br/>
																		“This is the message from the Amen, the faithful and true witness, who is the origin<br/>
																		of all that God has created.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																			<value>I know what you have done; I know that you are neither cold nor hot. How I wish you were either one or the other!</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																				<value>But because you are lukewarm, neither hot nor cold, I am going to spit you out of my mouth!</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																					<value>You say, ‘I am rich and well off; I have all I need.’ But you do not know how miserable and pitiful you are! You are poor, naked, and blind.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																						<value>I advise you, then, to buy gold from me, pure gold, in order to be rich. Buy also white clothing to dress yourself and cover up your shameful nakedness. Buy also some ointment to put on your eyes, so that you may see.<br/>
																						</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																							<value>I rebuke and punish all whom I love. Be in earnest, then, and turn from your sins.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																								<value>Listen! I stand at the door and knock; if any hear my voice and open the door, I will come into their house and eat with them, and they will eat with me.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>21</sup></key>
																									<value>To those who win the victory I will give the right to sit beside me on my throne, just as I have been victorious and now sit by my Father on his throne.<br/>
																									</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																										<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!”<br/>
																										</value>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</key>
			<value>
				<key><h3>The Message to Sardis</h3></key>
				<value><big>3</big></value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>1</sup></key>
					<value>“To the angel of the church in Sardis write:<br/>
					“This is the message from the one who has the seven spirits of God and the seven stars. I know what you are doing; I know that you have the reputation of being alive, even though you are dead!</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>2</sup></key>
						<value>So wake up, and strengthen what you still have before it dies completely. For I find that what you have done is not yet perfect in the sight of my God.<br/>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>3</sup></key>
							<value>Remember, then, what you were taught and what you heard; obey it and turn from your sins. If you do not wake up, I will come upon you like a thief, and you will not even know the time when I will come.</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>4</sup></key>
								<value>But a few of you there in Sardis have kept your clothes clean. You will walk with me, clothed in white, because you are worthy to do so.<br/>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>5</sup></key>
									<value>Those who win the victory will be clothed like this in white, and I will not remove their names from the book of the living. In the presence of my Father and of his angels I will declare openly that they belong to me.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>6</sup></key>
										<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
										<h3>The Message to Philadelphia</h3></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>7</sup></key>
											<value> “To the angel of the church in Philadelphia write:<br/>
											“This is the message from the one who is holy and true. He has the key that belonged to David, and when he opens a door, no one can close it, and when he closes it, no one can open it.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>8</sup></key>
												<value>I know what you do; I know that you have a little power; you have followed my teaching and have been faithful to me. I have opened a door in front of you, which no one can close.<br/>
												</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>9</sup></key>
													<value>Listen! As for that group that belongs to Satan, those liars who claim that they are Jews but are not, I will make them come and bow down at your feet. They will all know that I love you.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>10</sup></key>
														<value>Because you have kept my command to endure, I will also keep you safe from the time of trouble which is coming upon the world to test all the people on earth.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>11</sup></key>
															<value>I am coming soon. Keep safe what you have, so that no one will rob you of your victory prize.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																<value>I will make those who are victorious pillars in the temple of my God, and they will never leave it. I will write on them the name of my God and the name of the city of my God, the new Jerusalem, which will come down out of heaven from my God. I will also write on them my new name.<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																	<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!<br/>
																	<h3>The Message to Laodicea</h3></value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																		<value>“To the angel of the church in Laodicea write:<br/>
																		“This is the message from the Amen, the faithful and true witness, who is the origin<br/>
																		of all that God has created.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																			<value>I know what you have done; I know that you are neither cold nor hot. How I wish you were either one or the other!</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																				<value>But because you are lukewarm, neither hot nor cold, I am going to spit you out of my mouth!</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																					<value>You say, ‘I am rich and well off; I have all I need.’ But you do not know how miserable and pitiful you are! You are poor, naked, and blind.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																						<value>I advise you, then, to buy gold from me, pure gold, in order to be rich. Buy also white clothing to dress yourself and cover up your shameful nakedness. Buy also some ointment to put on your eyes, so that you may see.<br/>
																						</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																							<value>I rebuke and punish all whom I love. Be in earnest, then, and turn from your sins.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																								<value>Listen! I stand at the door and knock; if any hear my voice and open the door, I will come into their house and eat with them, and they will eat with me.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>21</sup></key>
																									<value>To those who win the victory I will give the right to sit beside me on my throne, just as I have been victorious and now sit by my Father on his throne.<br/>
																									</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																										<value>“If you have ears, then, listen to what the Spirit says to the churches!”<br/>
																										</value>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</value>
			<entry>
				<name>4</name>
				<key>
					<key>0.0</key>
					<value>0.0</value>
				</key>
				<value>
					<key>1.0</key>
					<value>1.0</value>
				</value>
				<entry>
					<name>5</name>
					<key>
						<key>0.0</key>
						<value>0.0</value>
					</key>
					<value>
						<key>1.0</key>
						<value>1.0</value>
					</value>
					<entry>
						<name>6</name>
						<key>
							<key>0.0</key>
							<value>0.0</value>
						</key>
						<value>
							<key>1.0</key>
							<value>1.0</value>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<name>7</name>
							<key>
								<key>0.0</key>
								<value>0.0</value>
							</key>
							<value>
								<key>1.0</key>
								<value>1.0</value>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<name>8</name>
								<key>
									<key>0.0</key>
									<value>0.0</value>
								</key>
								<value>
									<key>1.0</key>
									<value>1.0</value>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<name>9</name>
									<key>
										<key>0.0</key>
										<value>0.0</value>
									</key>
									<value>
										<key>1.0</key>
										<value>1.0</value>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<name>10</name>
										<key>
											<key>0.0</key>
											<value>0.0</value>
										</key>
										<value>
											<key>1.0</key>
											<value>1.0</value>
										</value>
										<entry>
											<name>11</name>
											<key>
												<key>0.0</key>
												<value>0.0</value>
											</key>
											<value>
												<key>1.0</key>
												<value>1.0</value>
											</value>
											<entry>
												<name>12</name>
												<key>
													<key>0.0</key>
													<value>0.0</value>
												</key>
												<value>
													<key>1.0</key>
													<value>1.0</value>
												</value>
												<entry>
													<name>13</name>
													<key>
														<key>0.0</key>
														<value>0.0</value>
													</key>
													<value>
														<key>1.0</key>
														<value>1.0</value>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<name>14</name>
														<key>
															<key>0.0</key>
															<value>0.0</value>
														</key>
														<value>
															<key>1.0</key>
															<value>1.0</value>
														</value>
														<entry>
															<name>15</name>
															<key>
																<key>0.0</key>
																<value>0.0</value>
															</key>
															<value>
																<key>1.0</key>
																<value>1.0</value>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<name>16</name>
																<key>
																	<key>0.0</key>
																	<value>0.0</value>
																</key>
																<value>
																	<key>1.0</key>
																	<value>1.0</value>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<name>17</name>
																	<key>
																		<key>0.0</key>
																		<value>0.0</value>
																	</key>
																	<value>
																		<key>1.0</key>
																		<value>1.0</value>
																	</value>
																	<entry>
																		<name>18</name>
																		<key>
																			<key>0.0</key>
																			<value>0.0</value>
																		</key>
																		<value>
																			<key>1.0</key>
																			<value>1.0</value>
																		</value>
																		<entry>
																			<name>19</name>
																			<key>
																				<key>0.0</key>
																				<value>0.0</value>
																			</key>
																			<value>
																				<key>1.0</key>
																				<value>1.0</value>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<name>20</name>
																				<key>
																					<key>0.0</key>
																					<value>0.0</value>
																				</key>
																				<value>
																					<key>1.0</key>
																					<value>1.0</value>
																				</value>
																				<entry>
																					<name>21</name>
																					<key>
																						<key>0.0</key>
																						<value>0.0</value>
																					</key>
																					<value>
																						<key>1.0</key>
																						<value>1.0</value>
																					</value>
																					<entry>
																						<name>22</name>
																						<key>
																							<key>0.0</key>
																							<value>0.0</value>
																						</key>
																						<value>
																							<key>1.0</key>
																							<value>1.0</value>
																						</value>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</entry>
	</entry>
</entry>