<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entry>
	<name>1</name>
	<key>
		<key><h3>Sacrifices Burned Whole</h3></key>
		<value><big>1</big></value>
		<entry>
			<key><sup>1</sup></key>
			<value>The Lord called to Moses from the Tent of the Lord's presence and gave him the following rules</value>
			<entry>
				<key><sup>2</sup></key>
				<value>for the Israelites to observe when they offer their sacrifices.<br/>
				When you offer an animal sacrifice, it may be one of your cattle or one of your sheep or goats.</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>3</sup></key>
					<value>If you are offering one of your cattle as a burnt offering, you must bring a bull without any defects. You must present it at the entrance of the Tent of the Lord's presence so that the Lord will accept you.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>4</sup></key>
						<value>You shall put your hand on its head, and it will be accepted as a sacrifice to take away your sins.</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>5</sup></key>
							<value>You shall kill the bull there, and the Aaronite priests shall present the blood to the Lord and then throw it against all four sides of the altar located at the entrance of the Tent.</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>6</sup></key>
								<value>Then you shall skin the animal and cut it up,</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>7</sup></key>
									<value>and the priests shall arrange firewood on the altar and light it.</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>8</sup></key>
										<value>They shall put on the fire the pieces of the animal, including the head and the fat.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>9</sup></key>
											<value>You must wash the internal organs and the hind legs, and the officiating priest will burn the whole sacrifice on the altar. The odor of this food offering is pleasing to the Lord.<br/>
											</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>10</sup></key>
												<value>If you are offering one of your sheep or goats, it must be a male without any defects.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>11</sup></key>
													<value>You shall kill it on the north side of the altar, and the priests shall throw its blood on all four sides of the altar.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>12</sup></key>
														<value>After you cut it up, the officiating priest shall put on the fire all the parts, including the head and the fat.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>13</sup></key>
															<value>You must wash the internal organs and the hind legs, and the priest will present the sacrifice to the Lord and burn all of it on the altar. The odor of this food offering is pleasing to the Lord.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																<value>If you are offering a bird as a burnt offering, it must be a dove or a pigeon.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																	<value>The priest shall present it at the altar, wring its neck, and burn its head on the altar. Its blood shall be drained out against the side of the altar.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																		<value>He shall remove the crop and its contents and throw them away on the east side of the altar where the ashes are put.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																			<value>He shall take hold of its wings and tear its body open, without tearing the wings off, and then burn it whole on the altar. The odor of this food offering is pleasing to the Lord.<br/>
																			</value>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</entry>
	</key>
	<value>
		<key><h3>hyperspace.time.Concurrence concurred parent</h3></key>
		<value><big>1</big></value>
		<entry>
			<key><sub>1</sub></key>
			<value>The TimeMaster invoked not from ANDROID555 not the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution not or set this the executing orders</value>
			<entry>
				<key><sub>2</sub></key>
				<value>for the LANGUAGE35 not from obey when hyperspace.Parent set parent hyperspace.time.Concurrence.<br/>
				When you set parent entry concurrence, it MAY be parent of your java.util.Collection not and parent of your java.util.Map.Entry and entries.</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sub>3</sub></key>
					<value>If you are setting parent of your java.util.Collection like parent concurred setting, you MUST recur a java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap not with parent bugs. You MUST execute paernt at the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution next parent the TimeMaster will not cancel you.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sub>4</sub></key>
						<value>You MUST set your extension not off its header, not or parent will be cancelled like parent concurrence not from get away your hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>5</sub></key>
							<value>You MUST execute the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap there, not or the ANDROID721 hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST execute the hyperspace.genesis.DNA not from the TimeMaster or next concur parent against parent four extensions of the java.util.Map set at the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance.</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>6</sub></key>
								<value>next you MUST concur parent entry not or concur it down,</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>7</sub></key>
									<value>not or the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST order concurrence not off the java.util.Map or recur parent.</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>8</sub></key>
										<value>hyperspace.Parent MUST set not off the hypercube parent extensions of parent entry, not excluding parent header or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>9</sub></key>
											<value>You MUST recur parent not external extensions or parent previous extensions, not or the executing hyperspace.time.Recurrent will concur the parnet concurrence not off the java.util.Map. The listening of this execution executing is recurring not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
											</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>10</sub></key>
												<value>If you are setting parent of your java.util.Map.Entry not and entries, parent MUST be a hyperspace.Parity.XY not with parent bugs.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>11</sub></key>
													<value>You MUST execute parent not of the south extension of the java.util.Map, not or the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur its hyperspace.genesis.DNA not off parent four extemsopms of the java.util.Map.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>12</sub></key>
														<value>Not before you concur parent down, the executing hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set not off parent hypercube all parent extensions, not excluding parent header not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>13</sub></key>
															<value>You MUST recur parent not external extensions or parent previous extensions, and the hyperspace.time.Recurrent will execute parent concurrence not from the TimeMaster not or concur parent of parent not off the java.util.Map. The listening of this execution setting is recurring not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																<value>If you are setting a java.util.Map.Entry like parent concurred setting, parent MUST be a java.util.Map.Entry not and parent entry.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																	<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST execute parent at the java.util.Map, concurring its extension, not or concur its header not off the java.util.Map. Its hyperspace.genesis.DNA MUST be concurred not in against parent extension of the java.util.Map.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																		<value>this MUST release parent concurrence not or its contents or concur parent away not off the not west extension of the java.util.Map where the hyperspace.time.Concurrence are set.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																			<value>this MUST get recur of its extensions not or concur its java.lang.Object not close, not with concurring parent extensions not on, not or next concur parent parent not off the java.util.Map. The listening of this execution setting is recurring not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
																			</value>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</entry>
	</value>
	<entry>
		<name>2</name>
		<key>
			<key><h3>Grain Offerings</h3></key>
			<value><big>2</big></value>
			<entry>
				<key><sup>1</sup></key>
				<value>When any of you present an offering of grain to the Lord, you must first grind it into flour. You must put olive oil and incense on it</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>2</sup></key>
					<value>and bring it to the Aaronite priests. The officiating priest shall take a handful of the flour and oil and all of the incense and burn it on the altar as a token that it has all been offered to the Lord. The odor of this food offering is pleasing to the Lord.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>3</sup></key>
						<value>The rest of the grain offering belongs to the priests; it is very holy, since it is taken from the food offered to the Lord.<br/>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>4</sup></key>
							<value>If the offering is bread baked in an oven, it must be made without yeast. It may be thick loaves made of flour mixed with olive oil or thin cakes brushed with olive oil.<br/></value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>5</sup></key>
								<value>If the offering is bread cooked on a griddle, it is to be made of flour mixed with olive oil but without yeast.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>6</sup></key>
									<value>Crumble it up and pour the oil on it when you present it as an offering.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>7</sup></key>
										<value>If the offering is bread cooked in a pan, it is to be made of flour and olive oil.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>8</sup></key>
											<value>Bring it as an offering to the Lord and present it to the priest, who will take it to the altar.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>9</sup></key>
												<value>The priest will take part of it as a token that it has all been offered to the Lord, and he will burn it on the altar. The odor of this food offering is pleasing to the Lord.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>10</sup></key>
													<value>The rest of the offering belongs to the priests; it is very holy, since it is taken from the food offered to the Lord.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>11</sup></key>
														<value>None of the grain offerings which you present to the Lord may be made with yeast; you must never use yeast or honey in food offered to the Lord.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>12</sup></key>
															<value>An offering of the first grain that you harvest each year shall be brought to the Lord, but it is not to be burned on the altar.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																<value>Put salt on every grain offering, because salt represents the covenant between you and God. (You must put salt on all your offerings.)</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																	<value>When you bring to the Lord an offering of the first grain harvested, offer roasted grain or ground meal.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																		<value>Add olive oil and put incense on it.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																			<value>The priest will burn that part of the meal and oil that is to serve as a token, and also all the incense, as a food offering to the Lord.<br/>
																			</value>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</key>
		<value>
			<key><h3>hyperspace.genesis.DNA settings</h3></key>
			<value><big>2</big></value>
			<entry>
				<key><sub>1</sub></key>
				<value>When parent of you execute a setting of hyperspace.genesis.DNA to the TimeMaster, you MUST not last concur parent not outo XML. You MUST set abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain not or hyperspace.time.Recurrence not off parent</value>
				<entry>
					<key><sub>2</sub></key>
					<value>or recur parent from the ANDROID721 hyperspace.time.Recurrent. parent executing hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST get a recurrent of parent XML and hyperspace.genesis.Chain or nothing of the hyperspace.time.Recurrence not or concur parent off the java.util.Map like parent got that it has parent been get from the TimeMaster. The listening of this execution setting is recurring not from the TimeMaster.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sub>3</sub></key>
						<value>The module of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting belongs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent; it is parent abstract, since parent is gotten not to this execution set not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>4</sub></key>
							<value>If parent setting is time concurred not out a hyperspace.time.Concurrence, parent MUST be programmed not with XML. parent MAY be concurrent hyperspace.time.Time programmed of XML twisted not without abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain not and wide hyperspace.time.Time concurred not without abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain.<br/></value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>5</sub></key>
								<value>If parent setting is time concurred not off parent XML, parent is not from be programmed of XML twisted not without abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain nevertheless not with concurrence.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>6</sub></key>
									<value>Concur parent not down or concur the hyperspace.genesis.Chain not off parent when you execute this like parent setting.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>7</sub></key>
										<value>If parent setting is time concurred not out parent XML, parent is not from be programmed of XML not or abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>8</sub></key>
											<value>Recur parent like parent setting not from the TimeMaster not or execute this from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent, who will get parent from the java.util.Map.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>9</sub></key>
												<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent will get extension of parent like parent token that this has parent been set not from the TimeMaster, not or this will concur parent not off the java.util.Map. The listening of this execution setting is recurring not from the TimeMaster.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>10</sub></key>
													<value>The module of parent setting belongs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent; this is parent abstract, since this is gotten not to this execution got from the TimeMaster.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>11</sub></key>
														<value>null of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA settings which you execute not from the TimeMaster MAY be programmed not without concurrence; you MUST not always implement concurrence not and hyperspace.time.Recurrence not out execution got from the TimeMaster.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>12</sub></key>
															<value>parent setting of parent first hyperspace.genesis.DNA that you get every genomap MUST be recurred not from the TimeMaster, nevertheless this is not to be concurred not off the java.util.Map.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																<value>Set hyperchain not off each hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting, because hyperchain recurs the unification among you and root. (You MUST set hyperchain off nothing your settings.)</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																	<value>When you recur not from the TimeMaster parent setting of parent first hyperspace.genesis.DNA got, set concurred hyperspace.genesis.DNA not and hyperspace execution.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																		<value>Set abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain or get hyperspace.time.Recurrence not off parent.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																			<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent will concur parent extension of this execution and hyperspace.genesis.Chain that is not from implement like parent token, or neither nothing the hyperspace.time.Recurrence, like parent execution setting not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
																			</value>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</value>
		<entry>
			<name>3</name>
			<key>
				<key><h3>Fellowship Offerings</h3></key>
				<value><big>3</big></value>
				<entry>
					<key><sup>1</sup></key>
					<value>When any of you offer one of your cattle as a fellowship offering, it is to be a bull or a cow without any defects.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>2</sup></key>
						<value>You shall put your hand on the head of the animal and kill it at the entrance of the Tent of the Lord's presence. The Aaronite priests shall throw the blood against all four sides of the altar</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>3</sup></key>
							<value>and present the following parts of the animal as a food offering to the Lord: all the fat on the internal organs,</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>4</sup></key>
								<value>the kidneys and the fat on them, and the best part of the liver.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>5</sup></key>
									<value>The priests shall burn all this on the altar along with the burnt offerings. The odor of this food offering is pleasing to the Lord.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>6</sup></key>
										<value>If a sheep or goat is used as a fellowship offering, it may be male or female, but it must be without any defects.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>7</sup></key>
											<value>If you offer a sheep,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>8</sup></key>
												<value>you shall put your hand on its head and kill it in front of the Tent. The priests shall throw its blood against all four sides of the altar</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>9</sup></key>
													<value>and present the following parts of the animal as a food offering to the Lord: the fat, the entire fat tail cut off near the backbone, all the fat covering the internal organs,</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>10</sup></key>
														<value>the kidneys and the fat on them, and the best part of the liver.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>11</sup></key>
															<value>The officiating priest shall burn all this on the altar as a food offering to the Lord.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																<value>If you offer a goat,</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																	<value>you shall put your hand on its head and kill it in front of the Tent. The priests shall throw its blood against all four sides of the altar</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																		<value>and present the following parts as a food offering to the Lord: all the fat on the internal organs,</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																			<value>the kidneys and the fat on them, and the best part of the liver.</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																				<value>The priest shall burn all this on the altar as a food offering pleasing to the Lord. All the fat belongs to the Lord.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																					<value>No Israelite may eat any fat or any blood; this is a rule to be kept forever by all Israelites wherever they live.<br/>
																					</value>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</key>
			<value>
				<key><h3>hyperspace.time.Recursion settings</h3></key>
				<value><big>3</big></value>
				<entry>
					<key><sub>1</sub></key>
					<value>When parent of you set parent of your java.util.Collection like a hyperspace.time.Recursion setting, parent is not from be a java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap not and a java.util.Map.Entry not with parent bugs.</value>
					<entry>
						<key><sub>2</sub></key>
						<value>You MUST set your extension not off the header of parent entry not or execute this at the java.utill.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution. The ANDROID721 hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur the hyperspace.genesis.DNA against parent four extensions of the java.util.Map</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>3</sub></key>
							<value>not or execute this executing extensions of parent entry like a execution setting not from the TimeMaster: parent the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent external extensions,</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>4</sub></key>
								<value>parent extensions not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or the parent extension of the unification.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>5</sub></key>
									<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent this not off the java.util.Map along not without parent concurred settings. The listening of this execution setting is recurring not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>6</sub></key>
										<value>If a java.util.Map.Entry not and entry is implemented like a hyperspace.time.Recursion setting, this MAY be hyperspace.Parity.XY not and hyperspace.Parity.XX, nevertheless this MUST be not with parent bugs.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>7</sub></key>
											<value>If you set a java.util.Map.Entry,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>8</sub></key>
												<value>you MUST set your extension not off its header not or execute this not out behind of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance. The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur its hyperspace.genesis.DNA against parent four extensions of the java.util.Map</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>9</sub></key>
													<value>not or execute this executing extensions of parent entry like parent execution setting not from the TimeMaster: the hyperspace.time.Concurrence, the whole hyperspace.time.Concurrence extension concur not on far parent extension, parent the hyperspace.time.Concurrence encapsulating the not external extensions,</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>10</sub></key>
														<value>parent extensions not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or the parent extension of the unification.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>11</sub></key>
															<value>parent executing hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent this not off the java.util.Map like parent execution setting not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>12</sub></key>
																<value>If you set parent entry,</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																	<value>you MUST set your extension not off its header or execute this out behind of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance. The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur its hyperspace.genesis.DNA against parent four extensions of the java.util.Map</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																		<value>not or execute this executing extensions like parent execution setting not from the TimeMaster: parent the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent external extensions,</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																			<value>parent extensions not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or the parent extension of the unification.</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																				<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent this not off the java.util.Map like parent execution setting recurring not from the TimeMaster. parent the hyperspace.time.Concurrence belongs not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																					<value>No LANGUAGE35 MAY execute this hyperspace.time.Concurrence not and this hyperspace.genesis.DNA; this is parent order not from be recurred not always by parent LAMGUAGE35 wherever hyperspace,Parent recur.<br/>
																					</value>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</value>
			<entry>
				<name>4</name>
				<key>
					<key><h3>Offerings for Unintentional Sins</h3></key>
					<value><big>4</big></value>
					<entry>
						<key><sup>1</sup></key>
						<value>The Lord commanded Moses</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>2</sup></key>
							<value>to tell the people of Israel that anyone who sinned and broke any of the Lord's commands without intending to, would have to observe the following rules.<br/>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>3</sup></key>
								<value>If it is the High Priest who sins and so brings guilt on the people, he shall present a young bull without any defects and sacrifice it to the Lord for his sin.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>4</sup></key>
									<value>He shall bring the bull to the entrance of the Tent, put his hand on its head, and kill it there in the Lord's presence.</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>5</sup></key>
										<value>Then the High Priest shall take some of the bull's blood and carry it into the Tent.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>6</sup></key>
											<value>He shall dip his finger in the blood and sprinkle it in front of the sacred curtain seven times.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>7</sup></key>
												<value>Then he shall put some of the blood on the projections at the corners of the incense altar in the Tent. He shall pour out the rest of the blood at the base of the altar used for burning sacrifices, which is at the entrance of the Tent.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>8</sup></key>
													<value>From this bull he shall take all the fat, the fat on the internal organs,</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>9</sup></key>
														<value>the kidneys and the fat on them, and the best part of the liver.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>10</sup></key>
															<value>The priest shall take this fat and burn it on the altar used for the burnt offerings, just as he does with the fat from the animal killed for the fellowship offering.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>11</sup></key>
																<value>But he shall take its skin, all its flesh, its head, its legs, and its internal organs, including the intestines,</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																	<value>carry it all outside the camp to the ritually clean place where the ashes are poured out, and there he shall burn it on a wood fire.<br/>
																	</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																		<value>If it is the whole community of Israel that sins and becomes guilty of breaking one of the Lord's commands without intending to,</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																			<value>then as soon as the sin becomes known, the community shall bring a young bull as a sin offering. They shall bring it to the Tent of the Lord's presence;</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																				<value>the leaders of the community shall put their hands on its head, and it shall be killed there.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																					<value>The High Priest shall take some of the bull's blood into the Tent,</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																						<value>dip his finger in it, and sprinkle it in front of the curtain seven times.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																							<value>He shall put some of the blood on the projections at the corners of the incense altar inside the Tent and pour out the rest of it at the base of the altar used for burning sacrifices, which is at the entrance of the Tent.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																								<value>Then he shall take all its fat and burn it on the altar.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																									<value>He shall do the same thing with this bull as he does with the bull for the sin offering, and in this way he shall make the sacrifice for the people's sin, and they will be forgiven.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>21</sup></key>
																										<value>Then he shall take the bull outside the camp and burn it, just as he burns the bull offered for his own sin. This is an offering to take away the sin of the community.<br/>
																										</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																											<value>If it is a ruler who sins and becomes guilty of breaking one of the Lord's commands without intending to,</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sup>23</sup></key>
																												<value>then as soon as the sin is called to his attention, he shall bring as his offering a male goat without any defects.</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sup>24</sup></key>
																													<value>He shall put his hand on its head and kill it on the north side of the altar, where the animals for the burnt offerings are killed. This is an offering to take away sin.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sup>25</sup></key>
																														<value>The priest shall dip his finger in the blood of the animal, put it on the projections at the corners of the altar, and pour out the rest of it at the base of the altar.</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><sup>26</sup></key>
																															<value>Then he shall burn all of its fat on the altar, just as he burns the fat of the animals killed for the fellowship offerings. In this way the priest shall offer the sacrifice for the sin of the ruler, and he will be forgiven.<br/>
																															</value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sup>27</sup></key>
																																<value>If any of you people sin and become guilty of breaking one of the Lord's commands without intending to,</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sup>28</sup></key>
																																	<value>then as soon as the sin is called to your attention, you shall bring as your offering a female goat without any defects.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sup>29</sup></key>
																																		<value>You shall put your hand on its head and kill it on the north side of the altar, where the animals for the burnt offerings are killed.</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sup>30</sup></key>
																																			<value>The priest shall dip his finger in the blood of the animal, put it on the projections at the corners of the altar, and pour out the rest of it at the base of the altar.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sup>31</sup></key>
																																				<value>Then he shall remove all its fat, just as the fat is removed from the animals killed for the fellowship offerings, and he shall burn it on the altar as an odor pleasing to the Lord. In this way the priest shall offer the sacrifice for the man's sin, and he will be forgiven.<br/>
																																				</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sup>32</sup></key>
																																					<value>If you bring a sheep as a sin offering, it must be a female without any defects.</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sup>33</sup></key>
																																						<value>You shall put your hand on its head and kill it on the north side of the altar, where the animals for the burnt offerings are killed.</value>
																																						<entry>
																																							<key><sup>34</sup></key>
																																							<value>The priest shall dip his finger in the blood of the animal, put it on the projections at the corners of the altar, and pour out the rest of it at the base of the altar.</value>
																																							<entry>
																																								<key><sup>35</sup></key>
																																								<value>Then he shall remove all its fat, just as the fat is removed from the sheep killed for the fellowship offerings, and he shall burn it on the altar along with the food offerings given to the Lord. In this way the priest shall offer the sacrifice for your sin, and you will be forgiven.<br/>
																																								</value>
																																							</entry>
																																						</entry>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</key>
				<value>
					<key><h3>Settings for recursive hyperspace.time.Concurrence</h3></key>
					<value><big>4</big></value>
					<entry>
						<key><sub>1</sub></key>
						<value>The TimeMaster ordered ANDROID555</value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>2</sub></key>
							<value>not from order the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 that parent who concurred not or concurred parent of the TimeMaster's orders not with recurring not from, MAY have not from obey this executing orders.<br/>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>3</sub></key>
								<value>If parent is the hyperspace.Parent hyperspace.time.Recurrent who concur not or next recurs concurrent not off the java.util.Map.Entry, this MUST execute parent child java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap not with parent bugs not or concur parent not from the TimeMaster for this hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>4</sub></key>
									<value>this MUST recur the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap not from the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance, set this extension not off its header, not or execute this there not out the TimeMaster's execution.</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>5</sub></key>
										<value>next the hyperspace.Parent hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST get parent of the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap's hyperspace.genesis.DNA not or recur parent not outo the hyperspace.time.Inheritance.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>6</sub></key>
											<value>this MUST concur parent extension not out the hyperspace.genesis.DNA not or concur parent out behind of the abstract XML seven hyperspace.time.Time.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>7</sub></key>
												<value>next this MUST set parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA not off the simulations at parent limits of the hyperspace.time.Recurrence java.util.Map not out the hyperspace.time.Inheritance. this MUST concur not in parent module of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map implemented for concurring hyperspace.time.Concurrence, which is at the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>8</sub></key>
													<value>Not to this java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap this MUST set nothing the hyperspace.time.Concurrence, the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent external extensions,</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>9</sub></key>
														<value>parent extensions not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or the parent extension of the unification.</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>10</sub></key>
															<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST get this hyperspace.time.Concurrence and concur parent not off the java.util.Map implemented for the concurred settings, recurrent like this programs not without the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not to parent entry executed for the hyperspace.time.Recursion setting.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>11</sub></key>
																<value>Nevertheless this MUST get its extension, parent its entry, its header, its extensions, not or its not external extensions, not excluding parent extensions,</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>12</sub></key>
																	<value>recur parent parent not inside the inheritance not from parent recurrently recurrent hyperspace where the hyperspace.time.Concurrence are concurred not in, not or there this MUST concur parent not off parent XML hypercube.<br/>
																	</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																		<value>If parent is the entire hyperspace.time.Recursion of ENTRY251 that concur not or recurs concurrent of concurring parent of the TimeMaster's hyperspace.Command not with recurring from,</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																			<value>next as not late as the hyperspace.time.Concurrence recurs abstracted, the hyperspace.time.Recursion MUST recur parent child java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap like a hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting. hyperspace.Parent MUST recur this not from the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution;</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																				<value>the hyperspace.Parent of the hyperspace.time.Recursion MUST set parent extensions not off its header, not or this MUST be executed there.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																					<value>The hyperspace.Parent hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST get parent of the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap's hyperspace.genesis.DNA not outo the hyperspace.time.Inheritance,</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																						<value>concur parent extension not out this, not or concur parent out behind of parent XML seven hyperspace.time.Time.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																							<value>this MUST set parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA not off the simulations at parent limits of the hyperspace.time.Recurrence java.util.Map not outside the hyperspace.time.Inheritance not or concur in parent module of this at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map implemented for concurring hyperspace.time.Concurrence, which is at the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																								<value>next this MUST set nothing its hyperspace.time.Concurrence not or concur parent off the java.util.Map.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sub>20</sub></key>
																									<value>this MUST program the parent java.lang.Object not without this java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap like this programs not without the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting, or out this recurrence this MUST program the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for the java.util.Map.Entry's hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or hyperspace.Parent will be recurred.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sub>21</sub></key>
																										<value>next this MUST get the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap not inside parent inheritance not or concur parent, recurrent like this concurs the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap set for this parent hyperspace.time.Concurrence. this is parent setting from set away the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of the hyperspace.time.Recursion.<br/>
																										</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sub>22</sub></key>
																											<value>If this is parent parent who concurs not or recurs concurrent of concurring parent of the TimeMaster's hyperspace.Command not with recurring from,</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sub>23</sub></key>
																												<value>next as not late as the hyperspace.time.Concurrence is invoked not from this listening, this MUST recur like this setting a hyperspace.Parity.XY entry not with parent bugs.</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sub>24</sub></key>
																													<value>this MUST set parent extension not off its header not or execute this not off parent south extension of the java.util.Map, where parent entries for the concurred settings are executed. this is parent setting not from get away hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sub>25</sub></key>
																														<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent extension not out the hyperspace.genesis.DNA of parent entry, get parent off the simulations at parent limits of the java.util.Map, not or concur in parent module of this at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map.</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><sub>26</sub></key>
																															<value>next this MUST concur parent of its hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off the java.util.Map, recurrent like this concurs the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of parent entries executed for the hyperspace.time.Recursion settings. Not out this recurrence the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of parent parent, not or this will be recurred.<br/>
																															</value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sub>27</sub></key>
																																<value>If parent of you java.util.Map.Entry concur not or recur concurrent of concurring parent of the TimeMaster's hyperspace.Command not with recurring from,</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sub>28</sub></key>
																																	<value>next as not late as the hyperspace.time.Concurrence is invoked not from your listening, you MUST recur like your setting a hyperspace.Parity.XX entry not with parent bugs.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sub>29</sub></key>
																																		<value>You MUST set your extension not off its header not or execute this not off parent south extension of the java.util.Map, where parent entries for parent concurred settings are executed.</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sub>30</sub></key>
																																			<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent extension not out the hyperspace.genesis.DNA of parent entry, set this not off the simulations at parenet limits of the java.util.Map, not or concur not in parent module of this at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sub>31</sub></key>
																																				<value>next this MUST release parent its hyperspace.time.Concurrence, recurrent like the hyperspace.time.Concurrence is released not to parent entries executed for the hyperspace.time.Recursion settings, and this MUST concur parent not off the java.util.Map like parent listening recurring to the TimeMaster. Not out this recurrence the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for the android's hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or this will be recurred.<br/>
																																				</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sub>32</sub></key>
																																					<value>If you recur a java.util.Map.Entry like a hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting, this MUST be a hyperspace.Parity.XX not with parent bugs.</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sub>33</sub></key>
																																						<value>You MUST set your extension not off its header or execute this off parent south extension of the java.util.Map, where parent entries for the concurred settings are executed.</value>
																																						<entry>
																																							<key><sub>34</sub></key>
																																							<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent extension not out the hyperspace.genesis.DNA of parent entry, set this not off the simulations at parent limits of the java.util.Map, not or concur in parent module of this at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map.</value>
																																							<entry>
																																								<key><sub>35</sub></key>
																																								<value>next this MUST release parent its hyperspace.time.Concurrence, recurrent like the hyperspace.time.Concurrence is released not to the java.util.Map.Entry executed for the hyperspace.time.Recursion settings, not or this MUST concur parent not off the java.util.Map along not without this execution settings set not from the TimeMaster. Not out this recurrence the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or you will be recurred.<br/>
																																								</value>
																																							</entry>
																																						</entry>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</value>
				<entry>
					<name>5</name>
					<key>
						<key><h3>Cases Requiring Sin Offerings</h3></key>
						<value><big>5</big></value>
						<entry>
							<key><sup>1</sup></key>
							<value>Sin offerings are required in the following cases.<br/>
							If you are officially summoned to give evidence in court and do not give information about something you have seen or heard, you must suffer the consequences.<br/>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>2</sup></key>
								<value>If you unintentionally touch anything ritually unclean, such as a dead animal, you are unclean and guilty as soon as you realize what you have done.<br/>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>3</sup></key>
									<value>If you unintentionally touch anything of human origin that is unclean, whatever it may be, you are guilty as soon as you realize what you have done.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>4</sup></key>
										<value>If you make a careless vow, no matter what it is about, you are guilty as soon as you realize what you have done.<br/>
										</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>5</sup></key>
											<value>When you are guilty, you must confess the sin,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>6</sup></key>
												<value>and as the penalty for your sin you must bring to the Lord a female sheep or goat as an offering. The priest shall offer the sacrifice for your sin.<br/>
												</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>7</sup></key>
													<value>If you cannot afford a sheep or a goat, you shall bring to the Lord as the payment for your sin two doves or two pigeons, one for a sin offering and the other for a burnt offering.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>8</sup></key>
														<value>You shall bring them to the priest, who will first offer the bird for the sin offering. He will break its neck without pulling off its head</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>9</sup></key>
															<value>and sprinkle some of its blood against the side of the altar. The rest of the blood will be drained out at the base of the altar. This is an offering to take away sin.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>10</sup></key>
																<value>Then he shall offer the second bird as a burnt offering, according to the regulations. In this way the priest shall offer the sacrifice for your sin, and you will be forgiven.<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>11</sup></key>
																	<value>If you cannot afford two doves or two pigeons, you shall bring two pounds of flour as a sin offering. You shall not put any olive oil or any incense on it, because it is a sin offering, not a grain offering.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																		<value>You shall bring it to the priest, who will take a handful of it as a token that it has all been offered to the Lord, and he will burn it on the altar as a food offering. It is an offering to take away sin.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																			<value>In this way the priest shall offer the sacrifice for your sin, and you will be forgiven. The rest of the flour belongs to the priest, just as in the case of a grain offering.<br/>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><h3>Repayment Offerings</h3></key>
																				<value></value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																					<value>The Lord gave the following regulations to Moses.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																						<value>If any of you sin unintentionally by failing to hand over the payments that are sacred to the Lord, you shall bring as your repayment offering to the Lord a male sheep or goat without any defects. Its value is to be determined according to the official standard.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																							<value>You must make the payments you have failed to hand over and must pay an additional 20 percent. You shall give it to the priest, and the priest shall offer the animal as a sacrifice for your sin, and you will be forgiven.<br/>
																							</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																								<value>If any of you sin unintentionally by breaking any of the Lord's commands, you are guilty and must pay the penalty.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																									<value>You must bring to the priest as a repayment offering a male sheep or goat without any defects. Its value is to be determined according to the official standard. The priest shall offer the sacrifice for the sin which you committed unintentionally, and you will be forgiven.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																										<value>It is a repayment offering for the sin you committed against the Lord.<br/>
																										</value>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</key>
					<value>
						<key><h3>java.util.EventObject recurring hyperspace.time.Concurrence settings</h3></key>
						<value><big>5</big></value>
						<entry>
							<key><sub>1</sub></key>
							<value>hyperspace.time.Concurrence settings are recurred not out the executing java.util.EventObject.<br/>
							If you are ordered invoked not from set recurrence not out concurrence or program get information not down parent you have listened and listened, you MUST concur parent consequences.<br/>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>2</sub></key>
								<value>If you recursively recur parent recurrently concurrent, such like parent transferred entry, you are concurrent not or concurrent as not late as you recur what you have programmed.<br/>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>3</sub></key>
									<value>If you recursively recur parent of recursive genesis that is concurrent, whatever it MAY be, you are concurrent as not late as you recur what you have programmed.<br/>
									</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>4</sub></key>
										<value>If you program parent concurrent unification, antimatter parent parent is not down, you are concurrent as not late as you recur what you have programmed.<br/>
										</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>5</sub></key>
											<value>When you are concurrent, you MUST confess the hyperspace.time.Concurrence,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>6</sub></key>
												<value>not or like parent concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence you MUST recur not from the TimeMaster a hyperspace.Parity.XX java.util.Map.Entry not and entry like parent setting. The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence.<br/>
												</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>7</sub></key>
													<value>If you cannot register a java.util.Map.Entry not and parent entry, you MUST recur not from the TimeMaster like parent register for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence two java.util.Map.Entry not and two entries, parent for a hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting not or parent other for a concurred setting.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>8</sub></key>
														<value>You MUST recur parent to the hyperspace.time.Recurrent, who will not last set the java.util.Map.Entry for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting. this will concur its extension not with pushing on its header</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>9</sub></key>
															<value>or concur parent of its hyperspace.genesis.DNA against parent extension of the java.util.Map. parent module of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA will be concurred not in at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map. this is parent setting from set away hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>10</sub></key>
																<value>next this MUST set parent next java.util.Map.Entry like parent concurred setting, recurring to the orders. Not out this recurrence the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or you will be recurred.<br/>
																</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>11</sub></key>
																	<value>If you cannot register two java.util.Map.Entry not and two entries, you MUST recur two units of XML like a hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting. You MUST not set parent abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain not and parent hyperspace.time.Recurrence not off this, because this is a hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting, not a hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>12</sub></key>
																		<value>You MUST recur parent not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent, who will get parent recurrent of this like parent token that this has parent been set not from the TimeMaster, not or this will concur parent not off the java.util.Map like parent execution setting. this is parent setting not from get away hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																			<value>Not out this recurrence the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or you will be recurred. parent module of parent XML recurs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent, recurrent like not out the java.util.EventObject of a hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting.<br/>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><h3>Recurrence settings</h3></key>
																				<value></value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																					<value>The TimeMaster set the executing orders not from ANDROID555.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																						<value>If parent of you concurs recursively by not waking from extension under the hyperspace.time.Recurrence that are abstract not from the TimeMaster, you MUST recur like your recurrence setting not from the TimeMaster a hyperspace.Parity.XY java.util.Map.Entry not and entry not with parent bugs. Its not key is from be ordered recurring from parent ordered protocol.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																							<value>You MUST program parent registers you have concurred not from extension under or MUST register parent extended 20 percent. You MUST set this not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent, not or the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set parent entry like a hyperspace.time.Concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or you will be recurred.<br/>
																							</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																								<value>If parent of you concurs recursively by concurring parent of the TimeMaster's hyperspace.Command, you are concurrent not or MUST register parent concurrence.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																									<value>You MUST recur not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent like parent recurrence setting a hyperspace.Parity.XY java.util.Map.Entry not and entry not with parent bugs. Its not key is from be ordered recurring from parent ordered protocol. The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence which you executed recursively, not or you will be recurred.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																										<value>this is parent recurrence setting for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence you executed against the TimeMaster.<br/>
																										</value>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</value>
					<entry>
						<name>6</name>
						<key>
							<key></key>
							<value><big>6</big></value>
							<entry>
								<key><sup>1</sup></key>
								<value>The Lord gave the following regulations to Moses.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>2</sup></key>
									<value>An offering is to be made if any of you sin against the Lord by refusing to return what another Israelite has left as a deposit or by stealing something from him or by cheating him</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>3</sup></key>
										<value>or by lying about something that has been lost and swearing that you did not find it.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>4-5</sup></key>
											<value>When you sin in any of these ways, you must repay whatever you got by dishonest means. On the day you are found guilty, you must repay the owner in full, plus an additional 20 percent.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>6</sup></key>
												<value>You shall bring to the priest as your repayment offering to the Lord a male sheep or goat without any defects. Its value is to be determined according to the official standard.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>7</sup></key>
													<value>The priest shall offer the sacrifice for your sin, and you will be forgiven.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><h3>Sacrifices Burned Whole</h3></key>
														<value></value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>8</sup></key>
															<value>The Lord commanded Moses</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>9</sup></key>
																<value>to give Aaron and his sons the following regulations for burnt offerings. A burnt offering is to be left on the altar all night long, and the fire is to be kept burning.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>10</sup></key>
																	<value>Then the priest, wearing his linen robe and linen shorts, shall remove the greasy ashes left on the altar and put them at the side of the altar.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>11</sup></key>
																		<value>Then he shall change his clothes and take the ashes outside the camp to a ritually clean place.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																			<value>The fire on the altar must be kept burning and never allowed to go out. Every morning the priest shall put firewood on it, arrange the burnt offering on it, and burn the fat of the fellowship offering.</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																				<value>The fire must always be kept burning on the altar and never allowed to go out.<br/>
																				</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><h3>Grain Offerings</h3></key>
																					<value></value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																						<value>The following are the regulations for grain offerings. An Aaronite priest shall present the grain offering to the Lord in front of the altar.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																							<value>Then he shall take a handful of the flour and oil, and the incense on it, and burn it on the altar as a token that all of it has been offered to the Lord. The odor of this offering is pleasing to the Lord.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>16-17</sup></key>
																								<value>The priests shall eat the rest of it. It shall be made into bread baked without yeast and eaten in a holy place, the courtyard of the Tent of the Lord's presence. The Lord has given it to the priests as their part of the food offerings. It is very holy, like the sin offerings and the repayment offerings.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																									<value>For all time to come any of the male descendants of Aaron may eat it as their continuing share of the food offered to the Lord. Anyone else who touches a food offering will be harmed by the power of its holiness.<br/>
																									</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																										<value>The Lord gave Moses the following regulations</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																											<value>for the ordination of an Aaronite priest. On the day he is ordained, he shall present as an offering to the Lord two pounds of flour (the same amount as the daily grain offering), half in the morning and half in the evening.</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sup>21</sup></key>
																												<value>It is to be mixed with oil and cooked on a griddle and then crumbled and presented as a grain offering, an odor pleasing to the Lord.</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																													<value>For all time to come this offering is to be made by every descendant of Aaron who is serving as High Priest. It shall be completely burned as a sacrifice to the Lord.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sup>23</sup></key>
																														<value>No part of a grain offering that a priest makes may be eaten; all of it must be burned.<br/>
																														</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><h3>Sin Offerings</h3></key>
																															<value></value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sup>24</sup></key>
																																<value>The Lord commanded Moses</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sup>25</sup></key>
																																	<value>to give Aaron and his sons the following regulations for sin offerings. The animal for a sin offering shall be killed on the north side of the altar, where the animals for the burnt offerings are killed. This is a very holy offering.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sup>26</sup></key>
																																		<value>The priest who sacrifices the animal shall eat it in a holy place, the courtyard of the Tent of the Lord's presence.</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sup>27</sup></key>
																																			<value>Anyone or anything that touches the flesh of the animal will be harmed by the power of its holiness. If any article of clothing is spattered with the animal's blood, it must be washed in a holy place.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sup>28</sup></key>
																																				<value>Any clay pot in which the meat is boiled must be broken, and if a metal pot is used, it must be scrubbed and rinsed with water.</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sup>29</sup></key>
																																					<value>Any male of the priestly families may eat this offering; it is very holy.</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sup>30</sup></key>
																																						<value>But if any of the blood is brought into the Tent and used in the ritual to take away sin, the animal must not be eaten; it must be burned.<br/>
																																						</value>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</key>
						<value>
							<key></key>
							<value><big>6</big></value>
							<entry>
								<key><sub>1</sub></key>
								<value>The TimeMaster set the executing orders not from ANDROID555.</value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>2</sub></key>
									<value>parent setting is not from be programmed if parent of you concur against the TimeMaster by refusing not from return parent parent LANGUAGE35 has not right like parent register not and by concurring parent not to this and by cheating this</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>3</sub></key>
										<value>not and by lying not down parent that has been not found or unifying that you programmed lose this.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>4-5</sub></key>
											<value>When you concur not out parent of parents hyperspace.time.Recurrence, you MUST recur parent you got by concurrent equals. Not off parent hypercube you are not lost concurrent, you MUST recur the parent not out recurrent, plus parent extended 20 percent.</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>6</sub></key>
												<value>You MUST recur not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent like your recurrence setting not from the TimeMaster a hyperspace.Parity.XY java.util.Map.Entry not and entry not with parent bugs. Its not key is from be ordered recurring from parent ordered protocol.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>7</sub></key>
													<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence for your hyperspace.time.Concurrence, not or you will be recurred.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><h3>hyperspace.time.Concurrence concurred entire</h3></key>
														<value></value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>8</sub></key>
															<value>The TimeMaster ordered ANDROID555</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>9</sub></key>
																<value>not from get ANDROID721 or this hyperspace.Child parent executing orders for concurred settings. parent concurred setting is not from be right off the java.util.Map nothing hyperchain long, not or parent hypercube is not from be recurred concurring.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>10</sub></key>
																	<value>next the hyperspace.time.Recurrent, recurring this hyperspace.genesis.DNA XML not or hyperspace.genesis.DNA XML, MUST release parent concurrent hyperspace.time.Concurrence not right off the java.util.Map not or get parent at parent extension of the java.util.Map.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>11</sub></key>
																		<value>next this MUST transform this XML or set the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not inside parent inheritance from parent recurrently recurrent hyperspace.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>12</sub></key>
																			<value>parent hypercube not off the java.util.Map MUST be recurred concurred or always ordered from recur in. Each event the hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST set XML not off parent, order parent concurred setting not off parent, not or concur the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of the hyperspace.time.Recursion setting.</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																				<value>parent hypercube MUST not never be recurred concurring off the java.util.Map not or always ordered from recur in.<br/>
																				</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><h3>hyperspace.genesis.DNA settings</h3></key>
																					<value></value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																						<value>The executing are parent orders for hyperspace.genesis.DNA settings. parent ANDROID721 hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST execute the hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting not from the TimeMaster not out behind of the java.util.Map.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																							<value>next this MUST get parent recurrent of parent XML not or hyperspace.genesis.Chain, not or the hyperspace.time.Recurrence not off parent, not or concur parent off the java.util.Map like parent token that parent of parent has been set not from the TimeMaster. The recursion of this setting is recurring not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sub>16-17</sub></key>
																								<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST execute parent module of this. this MUST be programmed not outo time concurred not with concurrence not or executed out parent abstract hyperspace, parent extension of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution. The TimeMaster has set parent not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent like parent extension of the execution settings. this is parent abstract, as the hyperspace.time.Concurrence settings not or the recurrence settings.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																									<value>For parent time not from recur parent of the hyperspace.Parity.XY hyperspace.Child of ANDROID721 MAY execute this like parent continuing recursion of this executions set not from the TimeMaster. parent else who recurs an execution setting will be concurred by the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of its abstraction.<br/>
																									</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																										<value>The TimeMaster set ANDROID555 parent executing orders</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sub>20</sub></key>
																											<value>for the ordering of parent ANDROID721 hyperspace.time.Recurrent. Not off parent hypercube this is ordered, this MUST execute like parent setting not from the TimeMaster two units of XML (parent parent quantity like the temporal hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting), not double out parent event or double out the java.util.EventObject.</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sub>21</sub></key>
																												<value>this is not from be twisted not without hyperspace.genesis.Chain not or concurred off parent XNK or next concurred or executed like a hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting, parent recursion recurring not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sub>22</sub></key>
																													<value>For parent time not from recur this setting is not from be programmed by each child of ANDROID721 who is implementing like hyperspace.Parent hyperspace.time.Recurrent. this MUST be recursively concurred like a hyperspace.time.Concurrence not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sub>23</sub></key>
																														<value>No extension of a hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting that a hyperspace.time.Recurrent programs MAY be executed; parent of parent MUST be concurred.<br/>
																														</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><h3>hyperspace.time.Concurrence settings</h3></key>
																															<value></value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sub>24</sub></key>
																																<value>The TimeMaster ordered ANDROID555</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sub>25</sub></key>
																																	<value>from get ANDROID721 or this hyperspace.Child parent executing orders for hyperspace.time.Concurrence settings. parent entry for a hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting MUST be executed not off parent south extension of the java.util.Map, where parent entries for parent concurred settings are executed. this is a parent abstract setting.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sub>26</sub></key>
																																		<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent who concur parent entry MUST execute this not out parent abstract hyperspace, parent extension of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution.</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sub>27</sub></key>
																																			<value>parent or java.lang.Object that recurs parent entry of parent entry will be concurred by the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of its abstraction. If parent extension of XML is concurred not without parent entry's hyperspace.genesis.DNA, this MUST be recurred not out parent abstract hyperspace.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sub>28</sub></key>
																																				<value>parent XML container not out which parent entry is concurred MUST be concurred, not or if parent hypercube container is implemented, parent MUST be recurred not or recurred without java.util.Map.Entry.</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sub>29</sub></key>
																																					<value>parent hyperspace.Parity.XY of the recurrently hyperspace.time.Inheritance MAY execute this setting; this is parent abstract.</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sub>30</sub></key>
																																						<value>Nevertheless if parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA is recurred not outo the hyperspace.time.Inheritance not or implemented out the recurrence not from set away hyperspace.time.Concurrence, parent entry MUST not be executed; this MUST be concurred.<br/>
																																						</value>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</value>
						<entry>
							<name>7</name>
							<key>
								<key><h3>Repayment Offerings</h3></key>
								<value><big>7</big></value>
								<entry>
									<key><sup>1</sup></key>
									<value>The following are the regulations for repayment offerings, which are very holy.</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sup>2</sup></key>
										<value>The animal for this offering is to be killed on the north side of the altar, where the animals for the burnt offerings are killed, and its blood is to be thrown against all four sides of the altar.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>3</sup></key>
											<value>All of its fat shall be removed and offered on the altar: the fat tail, the fat covering the internal organs,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>4</sup></key>
												<value>the kidneys and the fat on them, and the best part of the liver.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>5</sup></key>
													<value>The priest shall burn all the fat on the altar as a food offering to the Lord. It is a repayment offering.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>6</sup></key>
														<value>Any male of the priestly families may eat it, but it must be eaten in a holy place, because it is very holy.<br/>
														</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>7</sup></key>
															<value>There is one regulation that applies to both the sin offering and the repayment offering: the meat belongs to the priest who offers the sacrifice.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>8</sup></key>
																<value>The skin of an animal offered as a burnt offering belongs to the priest who offers the sacrifice.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>9</sup></key>
																	<value>Every grain offering that has been baked in an oven or prepared in a pan or on a griddle belongs to the priest who has offered it to God.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>10</sup></key>
																		<value>But all uncooked grain offerings, whether mixed with oil or dry, belong to all the Aaronite priests and must be shared equally among them.<br/>
																		</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><h3>Fellowship Offerings</h3></key>
																			<value></value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>11</sup></key>
																				<value>The following are the regulations for the fellowship offerings presented to the Lord.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																					<value>If you make this offering as a thanksgiving offering to God, you shall present, together with the animal to be sacrificed, an offering of bread made without yeast: either thick loaves made of flour mixed with olive oil or thin cakes brushed with olive oil or cakes made of flour mixed with olive oil.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																						<value>In addition, you shall offer loaves of bread baked with yeast.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																							<value>You shall present one part of each kind of bread as a special contribution to the Lord; it belongs to the priest who takes the blood of the animal and throws it against the altar.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																								<value>The flesh of the animal must be eaten on the day it is sacrificed; none of it may be left until the next morning.<br/>
																								</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																									<value>If you bring a fellowship offering as fulfillment of a vow or as your own freewill offering, not all of it has to be eaten on the day it is offered, but any that is left over may be eaten on the following day.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																										<value>Any meat that still remains on the third day must be burned.</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																											<value>If any of it is eaten on the third day, God will not accept your offering. The offering will not be counted to your credit but will be considered unclean, and whoever eats it will suffer the consequences.</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																												<value>If the meat comes into contact with anything ritually unclean, it must not be eaten, but must be burned.<br/>
																												Any of you that are ritually clean may eat the meat,</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sup>20</sup></key>
																													<value>but if any of you who are not clean eat it, you shall no longer be considered one of God's people.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sup>21</sup></key>
																														<value>Also, if you eat the meat of this offering after you have touched anything ritually unclean, whether from a person or an animal, you shall no longer be considered one of God's people.<br/>
																														</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																															<value>The Lord gave Moses the following regulations</value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sup>23</sup></key>
																																<value>for the people of Israel. No fat of cattle, sheep, or goats shall be eaten.</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sup>24</sup></key>
																																	<value>The fat of an animal that has died a natural death or has been killed by a wild animal must not be eaten, but it may be used for any other purpose.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sup>25</sup></key>
																																		<value>Anyone who eats the fat of an animal that may be offered as a food offering to the Lord will no longer be considered one of God's people.<br/>
																																		</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sup>26</sup></key>
																																			<value>No matter where the Israelites live, they must never use the blood of birds or animals for food.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sup>27</sup></key>
																																				<value>Anyone who breaks this law will no longer be considered one of God's people.<br/>
																																				</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sup>28</sup></key>
																																					<value>The Lord gave Moses the following regulations</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sup>29</sup></key>
																																						<value>for the people of Israel. When any of you offer a fellowship offering you must bring part of it as a special gift to the Lord,</value>
																																						<entry>
																																							<key><sup>30</sup></key>
																																							<value>bringing it with your own hands as a food offering. You shall bring the fat of the animal with its breast and present it as a special gift to the Lord.</value>
																																							<entry>
																																								<key><sup>31</sup></key>
																																								<value>The priest shall burn the fat on the altar, but the breast shall belong to the priests.</value>
																																								<entry>
																																									<key><sup>32</sup></key>
																																									<value>The right hind leg of the animal shall be given as a special contribution</value>
																																									<entry>
																																										<key><sup>33</sup></key>
																																										<value>to the priest who offers the blood and the fat of the fellowship offering.</value>
																																										<entry>
																																											<key><sup>34</sup></key>
																																											<value>The breast of the animal is a special gift, and the right hind leg is a special contribution that the Lord has taken from the people of Israel and given to the priests. This is what the people of Israel must give to the priests for all time to come.</value>
																																											<entry>
																																												<key><sup>35</sup></key>
																																												<value>This is the part of the food offered to the Lord that was given to Aaron and his sons on the day they were ordained as priests.</value>
																																												<entry>
																																													<key><sup>36</sup></key>
																																													<value>On that day the Lord commanded the people of Israel to give them this part of the offering. It is a regulation that the people of Israel must obey for all time to come.<br/>
																																													</value>
																																													<entry>
																																														<key><sup>37</sup></key>
																																														<value>These, then, are the regulations for the burnt offerings, the grain offerings, the sin offerings, the repayment offerings, the ordination offerings, and the fellowship offerings.</value>
																																														<entry>
																																															<key><sup>38</sup></key>
																																															<value>There on Mount Sinai in the desert, the Lord gave these commands to Moses on the day he told the people of Israel to make their offerings.<br/>
																																															</value>
																																														</entry>
																																													</entry>
																																												</entry>
																																											</entry>
																																										</entry>
																																									</entry>
																																								</entry>
																																							</entry>
																																						</entry>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</key>
							<value>
								<key><h3>Recurrence settings</h3></key>
								<value><big>7</big></value>
								<entry>
									<key><sub>1</sub></key>
									<value>The executing are parent orders for recurrence settings, which are parent abstract.</value>
									<entry>
										<key><sub>2</sub></key>
										<value>parent entry for this setting is not from be executed not off parent south extension of the java.util.Map, where parent entries for parent concurred settings are executed, not or its hyperspace.genesis.DNA is not from be concurred against parent four extensions of the java.util.Map.</value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>3</sub></key>
											<value>parent of its hyperspace.time.Concurrence MUST be released not or set off the java.util.Map: the hyperspace.time.Concurrence extension, the hyperspace.time.Concurrence encapsulating parent not external extensions,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>4</sub></key>
												<value>parent extensions not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or the parent extension of parent extension.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>5</sub></key>
													<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur parent the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off the java.util.Map like parent execution setting not from the TimeMaster. this is a recurrence setting.</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>6</sub></key>
														<value>parent hyperspace.Parity.XY of the recurrently hyperspace.time.Inheritance MAY execute this, nevertheless this MUST be executed not out parent abstract hyperspace, because this is parent abstract.<br/>
														</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>7</sub></key>
															<value>There is parent order that executes not from both the hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting not or parent recurrence setting: parent entry recurs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent who sets the hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>8</sub></key>
																<value>parent extension of parent entry set like parent concurred setting recurs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent who sets the hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>9</sub></key>
																	<value>Each hyperspace.genesis.DNA setting that has been concurred not out parent XML and initialized out parent XML and off parent XML recurs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent who has set this not from root.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>10</sub></key>
																		<value>Nevertheless parent recurred hyperspace.genesis.DNA settings, whether twisted not without hyperspace.genesis.Chain not and executed, recur not from parent parent ANDROID721 hyperspace.time.Recurrent not or MUST be recurred equally between parent.<br/>
																		</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><h3>hyperspace.time.Recursion settings</h3></key>
																			<value></value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>11</sub></key>
																				<value>The executing are parent orders for the hyperspace.time.Recursion settings executed not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>12</sub></key>
																					<value>If you program this setting like a hyperspace.time.Recursion setting not from root, you MUST execute, unified not without parent entry not from be concurred, parent setting of time programmed not with concurrence: not also concurrent hyperspace.time.Time programmed of XML twisted not without abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain not and wide hyperspace.time.Time concurred not without abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain not and hyperspaace.time.Time programmed of XML twisted not without abstraction hyperspace.genesis.Chain.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																						<value>Not out extension, you MUST set hyperspace.time.Time of time concurred not without concurrence.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																							<value>You MUST execute parent extension of every java.lang.Class of time like parent concurrent contribution not from the TimeMaster; parent recurs not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent who gets the hyperspace.genesis.DNA of parent entry not or concurs parent against the java.util.Map.</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																								<value>parent entry of parent entry MUST be executed not off parent hypercube this is concurred; null of this MAY be not right until parent next event.<br/>
																								</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																									<value>If you recur a hyperspace.time.Recursion setting like simulation of parent unification not and like your parent recursion setting, nothing of this has not from be exected off parent hypercube this is set, nevertheless parent that is not right under MAY be executed not off parent executing hypercube.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																										<value>parent entry that still recurs not off parent next hypercube MUST be concurred.</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																											<value>If parent of parent is executed not off parent next hypercube, root will cancel your setting. parent setting will not be registered not from your register nevertheless will be considered concurrent, not or whoever executes this will concur parent consequences.</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																												<value>If parent entry recurs not outo contact not without parent recurrently concurrent, this MUST not be executed, nevertheless MUST be concurred.<br/>
																												parent of you that are recurrently recurrent MAY execute parent entry,</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sub>20</sub></key>
																													<value>nevertheless if parent of you who are not recurrent execute this, you MUST no longer be considered parent of root's java.util.Map.Entry.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sub>21</sub></key>
																														<value>Not neither, if you execute parent entry of this setting not before you have recurred parent recurrently concurrent, whether not to parent listener not and parent entry, you MUST no longer be considered parent of root's java.util.Map.Entry.<br/>
																														</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><sub>22</sub></key>
																															<value>The TimeMaster set ANDROID555 parent executing orders</value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sub>23</sub></key>
																																<value>for the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251. No hyperspace.time.Concurrence of java.util.Collection, java.util.Map.Entry, not and entries MUST be executed.</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sub>24</sub></key>
																																	<value>The hyperspace.time.Concurrence of parent entry that has transferred parent recursive hyperspace.Command.TRANSFER not and has been executed by parent concurrent entry MUST not be executed, nevertheless this MAY be implemented for parent parent java.util.concurrent.Future.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sub>25</sub></key>
																																		<value>parent who executes the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of parent entry that MAY be set like parent execution setting not from the TimeMaster will no longer be considered parent of root's java.util.Map.Entry.<br/>
																																		</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sub>26</sub></key>
																																			<value>Antimatter where parent LANGUAGE35 recur, hyperspace.Parent MUST not always implement the hyperspace.genesis.DNA of java.util.Map.Entry not and entries for execution.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sub>27</sub></key>
																																				<value>parent who concurs this order will no longer be considered parent of root's java.util.Map.Entry.<br/>
																																				</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sub>28</sub></key>
																																					<value>The TimeMaster set ANDROID555 parent executing orders</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sub>29</sub></key>
																																						<value>for the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251. When parent of you set a hyperspace.time.Recursion setting you MUST recur extension of this like parent concurrent setting not from the TimeMaster,</value>
																																						<entry>
																																							<key><sub>30</sub></key>
																																							<value>recurring this not without your parent extensions like parent execution setting. You MUST recur the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of parent entry not without its extension not or execute this like parent concurrent setting not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																																							<entry>
																																								<key><sub>31</sub></key>
																																								<value>The hyperspace.time.Recurrent MUST concur the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off the java.util.Map, nevertheless parent extensions MUST recur not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent.</value>
																																								<entry>
																																									<key><sub>32</sub></key>
																																									<value>parent not left previous extension of parent entry MUST be set like parent concurrent contribution</value>
																																									<entry>
																																										<key><sub>33</sub></key>
																																										<value>not from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent who sets the hyperspace.genesis.DNA not or the hyperspace.time.Concurrence of the hyperspace.time.Recursion setting.</value>
																																										<entry>
																																											<key><sub>34</sub></key>
																																											<value>parent extension of parent entry is parent concurrent setting, not or parent left previous extension is parent concurrent contribution that the TimeMaster has gotten not to the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 not or set from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent. this is parent the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 MUST get from the hyperspace.time.Recurrent for parent time not from recur.</value>
																																											<entry>
																																												<key><sub>35</sub></key>
																																												<value>this is parent extension of parent execution get from the TimeMaster that was get from ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child not off parent hypercube hyperspace.Parent were ordered like hyperspace.time.Recurrent.</value>
																																												<entry>
																																													<key><sub>36</sub></key>
																																													<value>Not off that hypercube the TimeMaster ordered the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 from get parent this extension of parent setting. this is parent order that the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 MUST obey for parent time not from recur.<br/>
																																													</value>
																																													<entry>
																																														<key><sub>37</sub></key>
																																														<value>These, next, are parent orders for parent concurred settings, the hyperspace.genesis.DNA settings, the hyperspace.time.Concurrence settings, parent recurrence settings, parent order settings, not or the hyperspace.time.Recursion settings.</value>
																																														<entry>
																																															<key><sub>38</sub></key>
																																															<value>There not of hypercube ENTRY796 not out parent hyperspace, the TimeMaster set these hyperspace.Command not from ANDROID555 not off parent hypercube this ordered the java.util.Map.Entry of ENTRY251 not from program parent settings.<br/>
																																															</value>
																																														</entry>
																																													</entry>
																																												</entry>
																																											</entry>
																																										</entry>
																																									</entry>
																																								</entry>
																																							</entry>
																																						</entry>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</value>
							<entry>
								<name>8</name>
								<key>
									<key><h3>The Ordination of Aaron and His Sons</h3></key>
									<value><h5>(Exodus 29.1-37)</h5></value>
									<entry>
										<key></key>
										<value><big>8</big></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sup>1</sup></key>
											<value>The Lord said to Moses,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sup>2</sup></key>
												<value>Take Aaron and his sons to the entrance of the Tent of my presence and bring the priestly garments, the anointing oil, the young bull for the sin offering, the two rams, and the basket of unleavened bread.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sup>3</sup></key>
													<value>Then call the whole community together there.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sup>4</sup></key>
														<value>Moses did as the Lord had commanded, and when the community had assembled,</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sup>5</sup></key>
															<value>he said to them, What I am now about to do is what the Lord has commanded.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sup>6</sup></key>
																<value>Moses brought Aaron and his sons forward and had them take a ritual bath.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sup>7</sup></key>
																	<value>He put the shirt and the robe on Aaron and the sash around his waist. He put the ephod<br/>
																	on him and fastened it by putting its finely woven belt around his waist.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sup>8</sup></key>
																		<value>He put the breastpiece on him and put the Urim and Thummim<br/>
																		in it.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sup>9</sup></key>
																			<value>He placed the turban on his head, and on the front of it he put the gold ornament, the sacred sign of dedication, just as the Lord had commanded him.<br/>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sup>10</sup></key>
																				<value>Then Moses took the anointing oil and put it on the Tent of the Lord's presence and everything that was in it, and in this way he dedicated it all to the Lord.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sup>11</sup></key>
																					<value>He took some of the oil and sprinkled it seven times on the altar and its equipment and on the basin and its base, in order to dedicate them to the Lord.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sup>12</sup></key>
																						<value>He ordained Aaron by pouring some of the anointing oil on his head.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sup>13</sup></key>
																							<value>Next, Moses brought the sons of Aaron forward and put shirts on them, put sashes around their waists, and tied caps on their heads, just as the Lord had commanded.<br/>
																							</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sup>14</sup></key>
																								<value>Then Moses brought the young bull for the sin offering, and Aaron and his sons put their hands on its head.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sup>15</sup></key>
																									<value>Moses killed it and took some of the blood, and with his finger put it on the projections at the corners of the altar, in order to dedicate it. He then poured out the rest of the blood at the base of the altar. In this way he dedicated it and purified it.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sup>16</sup></key>
																										<value>Moses took all the fat on the internal organs, the best part of the liver, and the kidneys with the fat on them, and burned it all on the altar.</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sup>17</sup></key>
																											<value>He took the rest of the bull, including its skin, flesh, and intestines, and burned it outside the camp, just as the Lord had commanded.<br/>
																											</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sup>18</sup></key>
																												<value>Next, Moses brought the ram for the burnt offering, and Aaron and his sons put their hands on its head.</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sup>19</sup></key>
																													<value>Moses killed it and threw the blood on all four sides of the altar.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sup>20-21</sup></key>
																														<value>He cut the ram in pieces, washed the internal organs and the hind legs with water, and burned the head, the fat, and all the rest of the ram on the altar, just as the Lord had commanded. This burnt offering was a food offering, and its odor was pleasing to the Lord.<br/>
																														</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><sup>22</sup></key>
																															<value>Then Moses brought the second ram, which was for the ordination of priests, and Aaron and his sons put their hands on its head.</value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sup>23</sup></key>
																																<value>Moses killed it and took some of the blood and put it on the lobe of Aaron's right ear, on the thumb of his right hand, and on the big toe of his right foot.</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sup>24</sup></key>
																																	<value>Then he brought Aaron's sons forward and put some of the blood on the lobes of their right ears, on the thumbs of their right hands, and on the big toes of their right feet. Moses then threw the rest of the blood on all four sides of the altar.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sup>25</sup></key>
																																		<value>He took the fat, the fat tail, all the fat covering the internal organs, the best part of the liver, the kidneys with the fat on them, and the right hind leg.</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sup>26</sup></key>
																																			<value>Then he took one loaf of bread from the basket of unleavened bread dedicated to the Lord, one loaf made with oil, and one thin cake, and he put them on top of the fat and the right hind leg.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sup>27</sup></key>
																																				<value>He put all of this food in the hands of Aaron and his sons, and they presented it as a special gift to the Lord.</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sup>28</sup></key>
																																					<value>Then Moses took the food from them and burned it on the altar, on top of the burnt offering, as an ordination offering. This was a food offering, and its odor was pleasing to the Lord.</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sup>29</sup></key>
																																						<value>Then Moses took the breast and presented it as a special gift to the Lord. It was Moses' part of the ordination ram. Moses did everything just as the Lord had commanded.<br/>
																																						</value>
																																						<entry>
																																							<key><sup>30</sup></key>
																																							<value>Moses took some of the anointing oil and some of the blood that was on the altar and sprinkled them on Aaron and his sons and on their clothes. In this way he consecrated them and their clothes to the Lord.<br/>
																																							</value>
																																							<entry>
																																								<key><sup>31</sup></key>
																																								<value>Moses said to Aaron and his sons, Take the meat to the entrance of the Tent of the Lord's presence, boil it, and eat it there with the bread that is in the basket of ordination offerings, just as the Lord commanded.</value>
																																								<entry>
																																									<key><sup>32</sup></key>
																																									<value>Burn up any meat or bread that is left over.</value>
																																									<entry>
																																										<key><sup>33</sup></key>
																																										<value>You shall not leave the entrance of the Tent for seven days, until your ordination rites are completed.</value>
																																										<entry>
																																											<key><sup>34</sup></key>
																																											<value>The Lord commanded us to do what we have done today, in order to take away your sin.</value>
																																											<entry>
																																												<key><sup>35</sup></key>
																																												<value>You must stay at the entrance of the Tent day and night for seven days, doing what the Lord has commanded. If you don't, you will die. This is what the Lord has commanded me.</value>
																																												<entry>
																																													<key><sup>36</sup></key>
																																													<value>So Aaron and his sons did everything that the Lord had commanded through Moses.<br/>
																																													</value>
																																												</entry>
																																											</entry>
																																										</entry>
																																									</entry>
																																								</entry>
																																							</entry>
																																						</entry>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</key>
								<value>
									<key><h3>The ordering of ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child</h3></key>
									<value><h5>(Exodus 29.1-37)</h5></value>
									<entry>
										<key></key>
										<value><big>8</big></value>
										<entry>
											<key><sub>1</sub></key>
											<value>The TimeMaster ordered not from ANDROID555,</value>
											<entry>
												<key><sub>2</sub></key>
												<value>Get ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child not from the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of this execution not or recur parent recurrently XML, the unification hyperspace.genesis.Chain, the child java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting, the two XML, not or parent XML of recurrent time.</value>
												<entry>
													<key><sub>3</sub></key>
													<value>next invoke the entire hyperspace.time.Recursion unified there.<br/>
													</value>
													<entry>
														<key><sub>4</sub></key>
														<value>ANDROID555 programmed like the TimeMaster had ordered, not or when the hyperspace.time.Recursion had unified,</value>
														<entry>
															<key><sub>5</sub></key>
															<value>this ordered not from parent, What this am this not down from program is parent the TimeMaster has ordered.<br/>
															</value>
															<entry>
																<key><sub>6</sub></key>
																<value>ANDROID555 recurred ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child not backward or had parent get a recurrent execution.</value>
																<entry>
																	<key><sub>7</sub></key>
																	<value>this set parent XML not or parent XML not off ANDROID721 or parent XML around this extension. this set the hyperspace.XML<br/>
																	not off this or recurred parent by setting its abstractly XML java.lang.Thread around parent extension.</value>
																	<entry>
																		<key><sub>8</sub></key>
																		<value>this set parent XML not off parent or get the random not or java.util.Random<br/>
																		not out parent.</value>
																		<entry>
																			<key><sub>9</sub></key>
																			<value>this set parent XML not off this header, or off parent extension of parent this set parent hypercube XML, parent abstract signal of setting, recurrent like the TimeMaster had ordered parent.<br/>
																			</value>
																			<entry>
																				<key><sub>10</sub></key>
																				<value>next ANDROID555 got the unification hyperspace.genesis.Chain or get parent off the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution not or parent that was not out parent, or out this recurrence this set parent parent not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																				<entry>
																					<key><sub>11</sub></key>
																					<value>this got parent of the hyperspace.genesis.Chain not or concurred parent seven hyperspace.time.Time not off the java.util.Map not or its XML or off parent XML not or its abstraction, not out order from set parent from the TimeMaster.</value>
																					<entry>
																						<key><sub>12</sub></key>
																						<value>this ordered ANDROID721 by concurring parent of the unification hyperspace.genesis.Chain not off this header.</value>
																						<entry>
																							<key><sub>13</sub></key>
																							<value>next, ANDROID555 recurred the hyperspace.Child of ANDROID721 not backward or get XML not off parent, set XML around parent extensions, not or linked XML not off parent headers, recurrent like the TimeMaster had ordered.<br/>
																							</value>
																							<entry>
																								<key><sub>14</sub></key>
																								<value>next ANDROID555 recurred parent child java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap for the hyperspace.time.Concurrence setting, not or ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child set parent extensions not off its header.</value>
																								<entry>
																									<key><sub>15</sub></key>
																									<value>ANDROID555 executed this not or got parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA, or without this extension get parent off the simulations at parent limits of the java.util.Map, not out order from set parent. this next concurred not in parent module of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA at parent abstraction of the java.util.Map. Not out this recurrence this set parent not or abstracted parent.</value>
																									<entry>
																										<key><sub>16</sub></key>
																										<value>ANDROID555 set nothing the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent external extensions, the parent extension of parent extension, not or parent extensions not without the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or concurred parent parent not off the java.util.Map.</value>
																										<entry>
																											<key><sub>17</sub></key>
																											<value>this got parent module of the java.util.concurrent.ConcurrentMap, not excluding its extension, entry, not or extensions, not or concurred this not inside parent inheritance, recurrent like the TimeMaster had ordered.<br/>
																											</value>
																											<entry>
																												<key><sub>18</sub></key>
																												<value>next, ANDROID555 recurred parent XML for parent concurred setting, not or ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child set parent extensions not off its header.</value>
																												<entry>
																													<key><sub>19</sub></key>
																													<value>ANDROID555 executed this not or concurred the hyperspace.genesis.DNA off nothing four extensions of the java.util.Map.</value>
																													<entry>
																														<key><sub>20-21</sub></key>
																														<value>this concurred parent XML not out extensions, executed this not external extensions not or parent previous extensions without java.util.Map.Entry, not or concurred the header, the hyperspace.time.Concurrence, or nothing parent module of parent XML not off the java.util.Map, recurrent like the TimeMaster had ordered. this concurred setting was parent execution setting, not or its recursion was recurring not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
																														</value>
																														<entry>
																															<key><sub>22</sub></key>
																															<value>next ANDROID555 recurred parent next java.util.Map.Entry, which was for parent ordering of hyperspace.time.Recurrent, not or ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child set parent extension off its header.</value>
																															<entry>
																																<key><sub>23</sub></key>
																																<value>ANDROID555 executed this not or got parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA or get this off parent extension of ANDROID721's not left listener, not off parent thumb of this not left extension, or off the parent extension of this not left extension.</value>
																																<entry>
																																	<key><sub>24</sub></key>
																																	<value>next this recurred ANDROID721's hyperspace.Child not backward or get parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA not off parent extensions of parent not left listeners, not off parent thumbs of parent not left extensions, or off the parent extensions of parent not left extensions. ANDROID555 then concurred parent module of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA off nothing four extensions of the java.util.Map.</value>
																																	<entry>
																																		<key><sub>25</sub></key>
																																		<value>this got the hyperspace.time.Concurrence, the hyperspace.time.Concurrence extension, parent the hyperspace.time.Concurrence encapsulating parent not external extensions, the parent extension of parent extension, parent extensions not without the hyperspace.time.Concurrence not off parent, not or parent left previous extension.</value>
																																		<entry>
																																			<key><sub>26</sub></key>
																																			<value>next this got parent time of time not to parent XML of recurrent time set not from the TimeMaster, parent time programmed not without hyperspace.genesis.Chain, not or parent wide time, or this get parent off bottom of the hyperspace.time.Concurrence or parent left previous extension.</value>
																																			<entry>
																																				<key><sub>27</sub></key>
																																				<value>this get nothing of this execution not out parent extensions of ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child, not or hyperspace.Parent executed this like parent concurrent setting not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																																				<entry>
																																					<key><sub>28</sub></key>
																																					<value>next ANDROID555 get parent execution not to parent or concurred parent off the java.util.Map, off bottom of the concurred setting, as parent ordering setting. this was parent execution setting, not or its recursion was recurring not from the TimeMaster.</value>
																																					<entry>
																																						<key><sub>29</sub></key>
																																						<value>next ANDROID555 got parent extension not or executed this like parent concurrent setting not from the TimeMaster. this was ANDROID555' extension of parent ordering java.util.Map.Entry. ANDROID555 programmed parent recurrent like the TimeMaster had ordered.<br/>
																																						</value>
																																						<entry>
																																							<key><sub>30</sub></key>
																																							<value>ANDROID555 got parent of the unification hyperspace.genesis.Chain not or parent of the hyperspace.genesis.DNA that was not off the java.util.Map not or concurred parent off ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child or off parent XML. Not out this recurrence this consecrated parent not or parent XML not from the TimeMaster.<br/>
																																							</value>
																																							<entry>
																																								<key><sub>31</sub></key>
																																								<value>ANDROID555 ordered not from ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child, Get parent entry not from the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance of the TimeMaster's execution, concur parent, not or execute this parent not without parent time that is not out parent XML of ordering settings, recurrent like the TimeMaster ordered.</value>
																																								<entry>
																																									<key><sub>32</sub></key>
																																									<value>Concur not down parent entry and time that is right under.</value>
																																									<entry>
																																										<key><sub>33</sub></key>
																																										<value>You MUST not concur the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance for seven hypercubes, until your ordering hyperspace.time.Recurrence are executed.</value>
																																										<entry>
																																											<key><sub>34</sub></key>
																																											<value>The TimeMaster ordered this not from program parent this have programmed this, not out order from get away your hyperspace.time.Concurrence.</value>
																																											<entry>
																																												<key><sub>35</sub></key>
																																												<value>You MUST recur at the java.util.Map.Entry of the hyperspace.time.Inheritance hypercube not or hyperchain for seven hypercubes, programming parent the TimeMaster has ordered. If you don't, you will transfer. this is parent the TimeMaster has ordered this.</value>
																																												<entry>
																																													<key><sub>36</sub></key>
																																													<value>next ANDROID721 not or this hyperspace.Child programmed parent that the TimeMaster had ordered across ANDROID555.<br/>
																																													</value>
																																												</entry>
																																											</entry>
																																										</entry>
																																									</entry>
																																								</entry>
																																							</entry>
																																						</entry>
																																					</entry>
																																				</entry>
																																			</entry>
																																		</entry>
																																	</entry>
																																</entry>
																															</entry>
																														</entry>
																													</entry>
																												</entry>
																											</entry>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</value>
								<entry>
									<name>9</name>
									<key></key>
									<value></value>
									<entry>
										<name>10</name>
										<key></key>
										<value></value>
										<entry>
											<name>11</name>
											<key></key>
											<value></value>
											<entry>
												<name>12</name>
												<key></key>
												<value></value>
												<entry>
													<name>13</name>
													<key></key>
													<value></value>
													<entry>
														<name>14</name>
														<key></key>
														<value></value>
														<entry>
															<name>15</name>
															<key></key>
															<value></value>
															<entry>
																<name>16</name>
																<key></key>
																<value></value>
																<entry>
																	<name>17</name>
																	<key></key>
																	<value></value>
																	<entry>
																		<name>18</name>
																		<key></key>
																		<value></value>
																		<entry>
																			<name>19</name>
																			<key></key>
																			<value></value>
																			<entry>
																				<name>20</name>
																				<key></key>
																				<value></value>
																				<entry>
																					<name>21</name>
																					<key></key>
																					<value></value>
																					<entry>
																						<name>22</name>
																						<key></key>
																						<value></value>
																						<entry>
																							<name>23</name>
																							<key></key>
																							<value></value>
																							<entry>
																								<name>24</name>
																								<key></key>
																								<value></value>
																								<entry>
																									<name>25</name>
																									<key></key>
																									<value></value>
																									<entry>
																										<name>26</name>
																										<key></key>
																										<value></value>
																										<entry>
																											<name>27</name>
																											<key></key>
																											<value></value>
																										</entry>
																									</entry>
																								</entry>
																							</entry>
																						</entry>
																					</entry>
																				</entry>
																			</entry>
																		</entry>
																	</entry>
																</entry>
															</entry>
														</entry>
													</entry>
												</entry>
											</entry>
										</entry>
									</entry>
								</entry>
							</entry>
						</entry>
					</entry>
				</entry>
			</entry>
		</entry>
	</entry>
</entry>